Ladies and gentlemen, debut
皆様、デビューです
The second stage of Sy opponents
Sy対戦相手の第2ステージ
Please lead the Dr sprawl
博士の拡散を導いてください
yes
ええ
Is there abalone in it at night?
夜はアワビが入っているのかな？
No! What a pity!
いや、残念だ！
Very important!
とても重要です！
we got your opening
オープニングをいただきました
Welcome to this
ここへようこそ
Knowledge Banquet of the Month
今月の知識宴会
me a few months ago
数ヶ月前の私
After taking over the post of maternity home
助産院の引継ぎ後
one more job
もう一つの仕事
is to host the Knowledge Awards Banquet
ナレッジアワードの晩餐会を主催する予定です
it's good
それは良いです
happy work
幸せな仕事
Because I learn a lot every time
毎回とても勉強になるので
indeed a prize
まさに賞品
I believe this time is no exception
今回も例外ではないと思います
this time our
今回は私たちの
The main prize is Chen Zhiyi
主要賞はチェン・ジーイー
Dr. Chen Zhiyi
博士陳志義
He is a cell of the Chinese Academy
彼は中国アカデミーの細胞です
individual organisms
個々の生物
researcher at the Institute of
研究所の研究員
is in
いる
Culture University's Department of Oceanography Biology Group
文化大学海洋学部生物学グループ
get a bachelor's degree
学士号を取得する
later in Taiwan
その後台湾で
The joy of National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学の楽しさ
Institute of Science for a Master's Degree
修士号取得のための科学研究所
Then at National Taiwan University
その後、国立台湾大学へ
graduate School
研究所
It is a unit in the School of Life Sciences
生命科学部のユニットです
get a doctorate
博士号を取得する
Then he went to a very famous research institute in the UK
それから彼はイギリスの非常に有名な研究機関に行きました。
Call the Sanger Institute
サンガー研究所に電話する
Sanger won the Nobel Prize
サンガー氏がノーベル賞を受賞
for DNA sequencing
DNA配列決定用
the researcher who won the nobel prize
ノーベル賞を受賞した研究者
the scholar
学者
He is his Institute
彼は彼の研究所です
And in 2003 to the Institute of Zoology of Central Plains Institute
そして2003年にセントラルプレーンズ研究所の動物学研究所へ
This institute is now
この研究所は現在、
Cell Individual Biology Institute
細胞個体生物学研究所
Working at Linhai Research Station
臨海研究ステーションで働く
Now a researcher at that institute
現在はその研究所の研究員
Dr Chen has studied marine life for many years
チェン博士は長年海洋生物を研究してきた
Antibacterial ecology
抗菌エコロジー
that's his topic today
それが今日の彼の話題です
Fluorescence
蛍光
admiring the earth
地球を賞賛する
do research and development work
研究開発の仕事をする
I don't know if today will be better than these few
今日がこの数人よりも良いかどうかはわかりません
That's a very sad hope
それはとても悲しい希望です
Maybe
多分
In the future, you can also get from him
将来的には、彼から得ることもできます
Learn more about this very wronged one
この非常に不当な扱いを受けた事件について詳しく知る
the result of his research and development
彼の研究開発の結果
then he
そして、彼が
Dr. Chen
チェン博士
won many awards
多くの賞を受賞した
include
含む
Academician Yang Jiangfa
学者ヤン・ジャンファ
Outstanding Young Scholar Award in Agricultural Sciences
農学分野優秀若手研究者賞
in the National Innovation Awards
全米イノベーション賞で
he also used to be
彼もかつてはそうでした
Director of Taiwan Society of Marine Biotechnology
台湾海洋生物工学学会理事
OK, then we give warm applause
OK、温かい拍手を送りましょう
welcome thank you dr chen
ようこそ、ありがとう、チェン博士
Thank you Vice President for your report
副社長、ご報告ありがとうございました
Today is
今日は
The first knowledge missing in the end of the year
年末に足りない知識第一弾
first knowledge miss
最初の知識ミス
I'm here to say goodbye to everyone
みんなに別れを告げるためにここに来ました
Hope you all have a happy new year and all the best
皆様も良い新年をお迎えください。
Thank you all very much for coming here tonight to listen to knowledge miss
今夜ナレッジミスを聞きにここに来ていただきありがとうございます
There is what I talked about eating fish today but not
今日は魚を食べることについて話しましたが、そうではありません
Antimicrobial status of fish could be cancer-fighting
魚の抗菌状態は癌と闘う可能性がある
or antimicrobial psychotropic drugs
または抗菌性向精神薬
then i will be silent
それなら私は黙ります
I am from Jiao Township, Yilan County
私は宜蘭県焦郷の出身です
We have a forest sea research station over there
あそこに森林海研究所があります
Generally, you may be unfamiliar with the Linhai Research Station
一般に、臨海研究ステーションについてはあまり馴染みがないかもしれません。
But wait a minute we have a few eras
でもちょっと待ってください、私たちにはいくつかの時代があります
Let me introduce you to the Linhai Research Station
臨海研究ステーションをご紹介します
then i just
那我剛
I was just outside and the deputy dean asked everyone a question
私はちょうど外に出ていて、副学部長がみんなに質問しました
Tell me, have you eaten any fish tonight?
教えてください、今夜魚を食べましたか？
that's okay
大丈夫
I asked everyone if you have eaten fish like this today
今日はこんな魚を食べましたか？とみんなに聞いてみた
I think Yilan County is becoming more and more important
宜蘭県はますます重要になってきていると思います
a source of food
食料源
Especially now that everyone pays attention to health preservation
特に今は誰もが健康維持に注目しています
And recently there is love flu
そして最近はラブインフルも流行ってます
killed a bunch of geese
ガチョウの群れを殺しました
killed a bunch of chickens
鶏をたくさん殺した
pressure age
年
I can't tell the difference between the ear and the ear
耳と耳の区別がつかない
Then the best way is to eat fish
それなら魚を食べるのが一番いいよ
So the topic I'm talking about today
それで今日私が話すテーマは
I hope everyone will go back in the future
将来みんなが戻ってくることを願っています
can eat more fish
もっと魚を食べられる
Then help our water mountain farming industry in Taiwan
そして台湾の水山農業を支援してください
can develop with us
私たちと一緒に発展できる
Then we can produce more relevant research output in our marine biotechnology
そうすれば、海洋バイオテクノロジーにおいてより関連性の高い研究成果を生み出すことができます。
To take care of everyone's fasting on the food measurement
みんなの断食時の食事測定に気を配る
Alright, so today we are going to talk about what is called the anti-ying platform
さて、今日はいわゆるアンチインプラットフォームについて話します
That is, the anti-ying platform is a very interesting thing
つまり、アンチインプラットフォームは非常に興味深いものです
Let me tell you first, ask if you eat fish
まず教えてください、魚を食べるかどうか聞いてください
I think everyone must have seen these kinds of fish in the vegetable market
皆さんも青果市場でこんな魚を見たことがあると思います。
Except for this fish, everyone may be unfamiliar
この魚以外はあまり馴染みのない魚かもしれません
Everyone must have seen grouper
誰もがハタを見たことがあるはず
Yes, everyone has seen black abalone, right?
そう、皆さんも黒いアワビを見たことがあるでしょう？
when i went to the market
市場に行ったとき
My mother buys black abalone or buys these fish
母は黒アワビかこれらの魚を買います
he must tell me
彼は私に言わなければなりません
That salmon wheel, that wheel isn't good
そのサーモンホイール、そのホイールは良くありません
right, is that so
そうですか、そうですか
So put the salmon wheel in the case of the wheel
サーモンホイールをケースのホイールの下に置きます
Why is this fish sick?
なぜこの魚は病気なのですか？
may have been ill before his death
死ぬ前に病気だったのかもしれない
The sickness is in the aquatic oxygen body
病気は水中の酸素体にある
Fish diseases are somewhat similar to human diseases
魚の病気は人間の病気に似ている
Then this black abalone and this fish like flounder
それからこの黒アワビとこのヒラメのような魚
I'm going to report to you now
今からご報告させていただきます
Because I first write the names of these anti-Philippine sellers here
なぜなら、私は最初にこれらの反フィリピン販売者の名前をここに書くからです。
because everyone can know
誰もが知ることができるので
Let's wait and we'll introduce these protagonists to you
メインキャラクターを紹介しますのでお待ちください
We translate it into EBCD
EBCDに変換します
Because its English name is EBCD1
英語名はEBCD1なので
Its content is to hope that everyone can see the anti-Philippine sales
その内容は、反フィリピンセールスを皆さんに見てもらいたいというものです。
know that it will give B to E in the future
将来的にBがEに与えられることを知っている
So I translated it into this Chinese
それで私はそれを中国語に翻訳しました
on top of the turtle fish
亀の魚の上に
This is our common Niroka turtle fish
これは私たちの一般的なニロカカメの魚です
that turtle fish
あの亀の魚
It's Moshan Piccolo Turtle Fish
モーシャンピッコロタートルフィッシュです
They all have different anti-Philippines
彼らは皆、異なる反フィリピンを持っています
name sold against philippines
フィリピンに対して売られた名前
will have different names for different fish species
魚種ごとに異なる名前が付けられます
But because of its structure in different fish
しかし、魚の構造が異なるため、
is also different
も違います
Each anti-philippine is sold on a variety of different fish
それぞれの抗フィリピンはさまざまな魚で販売されています
it will have different functions
さまざまな機能があるでしょう
I'll report back to you later
後ほどまたご報告させていただきます
Now let me tell you an interesting story
さて、面白い話をしましょう
Why do we have to tell the story of Shui Shanyang
なぜ山陽水の物語を語らなければならないのか
I ran away to make a cup of wine.
私はワインを作るために逃げました。
I'm going to report to you now
今からご報告させていただきます
Nashuishanyang is the farming industry of grouper
那水山陽はハタの養殖業です
Taiwan's aquaculture aquaculture is very meticulous
台湾の養殖はとても丁寧です
you may not know
あなたは知らないかもしれません
Usually we may take the car to the maintenance shop
通常、車を整備工場に持ち込むことができます
A master can do a lot
マスターはたくさんのことができる
Let's say we go to the Ford service shop
フォードのサービスショップに行ったとします。
This master who may receive you
あなたを迎えてくれるこのマスターは
The whole car can be refueled and maintained
車全体に給油とメンテナンスが可能
But not in the year of the aquaculture industry
しかし、水産養殖産業の年ではありません
each different region
それぞれ異なる地域
every different period
異なる期間ごとに
it will have different breeders
違うブリーダーがいるだろう
Or breeding professionals to do farming work
または、農作業を行う繁殖専門家
In this picture, let me tell you
この写真で言わせてください
This is a grouper breeding process
これがハタの繁殖過程です
grouper it has what is called inch seconds
ハタにはインチ秒と呼ばれるものがあります
Of course at different times
もちろん違う時期でも
For example, this time only the time to eat mosquitoes
例えば今回は蚊を食べる時間だけ
Or the time to eat bee-snapped shrimp
あるいは蜂で捕れたエビを食べる時間
in different periods
さまざまな時期に
They all have different bacterial infections
彼らは皆、異なる細菌感染症を患っています
or viral infection
またはウイルス感染
For example, the grouper mainly has many
例えば、ハタ類は主に、
neurochemotherapy virus
ニューロケモウイルス
or have many bacterial infections
または多くの細菌感染症を患っている
e.g. fungal infection
例：真菌感染症
or so-called intense infection
またはいわゆる強力な感染症
or other infections such as pointworm
または点虫などの他の感染症
The lethality of these infections
これらの感染症の致死性
In fact, some have reached the so-called 100% fatality rate
実際、いわゆる致死率100%に達している人もいます。
Wait a minute and I will report a Hu Jun to everyone
ちょっと待ってください。フー・ジュンについて皆さんに報告します。
A Hu Jun made in our laboratory
研究室で作ったHu Jun
This Hu Jun is my last from college
このフー・ジュンが私の大学最後の人です
Obtained by Mr. Chen Junyao's laboratory
陳君耀氏の研究室より入手
This Hu Jun is very interesting
このフー・ジュンはとても興味深いです
You may not believe that we are sick
私たちが病気だなんて信じられないかもしれません
we are sick
私たちは病気です
live in hospital
病院に住んでいます
The hospital may also give you first aid and antibiotic treatment
病院では応急処置や抗生物質による治療も受けられる場合があります
come soon
すぐに来る
I'll talk about the proxy certificate later
プロキシ証明書については後ほど説明します
or acute
または急性
Acute pharmacology certificate
急性薬理証明書
Maybe in about a week, people's lives will be goodbye
たぶんあと一週間くらいで人々の命に別れが来るだろう
But do you believe it?
でも信じますか？
From our discovery of infection
感染の発見から
People who may have raised fish before could not understand
これまで魚を飼育したことがある人には理解できないだろう
how did this fish die
この魚はどうやって死んだのか
But he found that within 24 hours the fish in the whole area
しかし、彼は24時間以内にその地域全体の魚が絶滅したことを発見しました。
all will die for you
すべてはあなたのために死ぬでしょう
Then die and show you later
それから死んで、後で見せてください
you may see
あなたは見るかもしれません
some fish just cuddle fish
ただ魚を抱きしめるだけの魚もいる
ok
Ok
we'll talk next
次に話しましょう
When I went to Linghai Research Station
陵海研究基地に行った時のこと
When I first went to Linghai Research Station
初めて臨海研究基地に行ったとき
There is an interesting story that
面白い話があって、
We hope that at Linghai Research Station
陵海研究ステーションでそれを願っています
Some are the same as Taiwan carry
一部台湾キャリーと同じ
A job that can assist Taiwan's water mountain farming industry
台湾の水山農業を支援できる仕事
Because everyone eats fish like everyone sees
誰もが見るように魚を食べるので
have many emotions
たくさんの感情を持っている
that duck or goose will die
あのアヒルかガチョウは死ぬだろう
no robin dies
ロビンは死なない
so at that time
だからその時は
Director Guo Qingyin will tell me one thing
グオ・チンイン監督が一つ教えてください
what he wishes to be able to do
彼ができるようになりたいこと
make an early morning thing
早朝のものを作る
Able to assist Taiwan's water mountain farming industry
台湾の水山農業を支援できる
The problem of allowing illness
病気を許すことの問題
Then I wanted to say
それから言いたかったのは
how do i solve it
どうすれば解決できますか
What kinds of infections?
どのような種類の感染症ですか?
virus infection at that time
その時のウイルス感染
In my press release called The Laboratory of Inorganic Therapy
私のプレスリリースでは「無機療法研究所」と題されています。
have done well
よくやった
i think i do virus infection maybe
たぶんウイルス感染してると思う
So I think
それで私は思います
Bacterial infection may be a very interesting thing
細菌感染って面白いかもしれない
Because bacteria can kill invisible
細菌は目に見えないものを殺す可能性があるため
But it is possible to use a
しかし、それを使用することは可能です
a tiny bacterium
小さな細菌
it allows fish
それは魚を許可します
or cause disease in living things
または生物に病気を引き起こす
That's a disease Hu Jun got
それはフー・ジュンが患った病気です
It's a picture taken from the internet
ネットから拾った写真です
in the grouper or stack
ハタまたはスタックで
or Elephant Gauge
またはエレファントゲージ
You can see when Hu Jun is infected
Hu Junがいつ感染するかがわかります
In case of swelling
腫れの場合
In fact, this is because when the later outbreak
実際、これはその後の感染拡大の際に、
it inhales and reproduces in large numbers
吸い込んで大量に繁殖する
lots of splits
たくさんの分割
Then such a sudden illness occurs in Su Ni
そんな時、スニに突然の病気が起こる。
we help
私達は助けます
in case of acute illness
急性疾患の場合
just to give medicine
薬を与えるためだけに
From the concept of farming
農業という概念から
For example, I went to university from inside
たとえば、私は内から大学に行きました。
The concept of farming in those days
当時の農業の概念
In fact, we were raising grass shrimp at that time
実は当時グラスシュリンプを飼育していました
or raise some fish
または魚を育てるか
you may not know
あなたは知らないかもしれません
in their farming industry
彼らの農業業界では
all in cash
すべて現金で
at that time in university
当時大学時代
Just go to the aquaculture area to implement
養殖場に行って実装するだけ
When I went there to see how people raise fish
魚の育て方を見に行ったとき
I just discovered aquarium farming later
後になって水族館の養殖を知りました
It's a very shallow industry
とても浅い業界です
but
しかし
at that moment
その瞬間に
What to do if the fish is sick
魚が病気になったらどうするか
as I just reported to you
先ほどご報告したとおり
one night
ある夜
if all you raise
あなたがすべて上げれば
All 10,000 silky fish are fighting
10,000匹のウコギ全員が戦っている
look
見て
Then you don't feel very
そうすると、あまり気分が良くなくなります
very frustrated
とてもイライラした
those fish
あの魚たち
if not dying
死ななければ
before you die
あなたが死ぬ前に
because what will do ? drug
だってどうするの? 薬
What is drugging?
薬漬けとは何ですか？
Just give some chemicals or antibiotics
化学物質や抗生物質を与えるだけです
to treat these infections
これらの感染症を治療するために
bacterial infection
細菌感染
Let me introduce to you first
まずはご紹介させていただきます
aquaculture once upon a time
昔々の水産養殖
Chemical reagents commonly used in the past
過去によく使われていた化学試薬
For example, peacock eating worry
たとえば、孔雀が食べる心配
or antibiotics
または抗生物質
For example, this antibiotic
たとえば、この抗生物質は、
N-O killing heart
N-O キリングハート
It is a medicine for animals
動物用の薬です
These things will be mixed in the ingredients
こういったものが材料に混ざっていきます
forehead
額
Then you go to therapy for five days
それから5日間の治療に行きます
your fish will be fine
あなたの魚は大丈夫です
Why is it good? For example, peacock eats worry
なぜそれが良いのですか? たとえば、クジャクは心配を食べます。
Klebsiella spp
クレブシエラ属
many different bacteria
多くの異なる細菌
It has a bactericidal effect
殺菌効果があります
but
しかし
everyone knows
みんな知ってる
these things will
これらのことは
coping with the food chain
食物連鎖に対処する
let everyone see
みんなに見てもらいましょう
horseshoe perch
馬菌尿鱸
Very shiny fish eaten into the stomach
非常に明るい魚が胃に食い込まれました
These things will also eat into your stomach
こういったものもお腹に食い込んでしまいます
so
それで
So what's going on? Bacteria in the natural environment
では何が起こっているのでしょうか? 自然環境中の細菌
So-called drug resistance and limited drug production
いわゆる薬剤耐性と薬剤生産の制限
These two things deeply affect what we will talk about later
これら 2 つのことは、後で説明することに深く影響します
Why? Because bacteria it mutates
なぜか? 細菌が変異するからです
it will survive
それは生き残るだろう
Just like us human beings also in order to survive
私たち人間も同じように生きていくために
we will work very hard
私たちは一生懸命働きます
work hard
一生懸命働く
Bacteria will also work very hard
菌も頑張ってくれますよ
survive
生き残る
When a drug develops a resistance or drug miscarriage
薬剤耐性が生じた場合や薬剤流産が発生した場合
in this natural environment
この自然環境の中で
we're in big trouble
私たちは大きな問題に直面しています
Because of the relationship through the food chain
食物連鎖でつながっているので
will enter the human body
人体に入ります
Let's talk about sex
セックスについて話しましょう
CGMP medicines
CGMP医薬品
it has a product called mecon cream
メコンクリームという商品があります
Everyone probably used it
きっとみんな使ってたんだろうな
In the medicine on the Department of Human Medicine
人間医学科の医学で
You can see that it's all made of antibiotics.
すべて抗生物質でできていることがわかります。
For example, Neumicin
たとえば、ノイマイシン
this drug
この薬
You can see it's all clearly written
はっきりと書かれているのがわかります
now you go inside the pharmacy
今度は薬局の中に入ります
when buying any medicine
薬を買うとき
They will all be in the drug
彼らは皆麻薬中毒になるだろう
on the trick table
トリックテーブルの上に
will be detailed in the form
フォームに詳しく記載されます
what are these drugs for
これらの薬は何のためにありますか
it will also tell you about its sex
性別についても教えてくれます
What are the indications
兆候は何ですか
He will also adopt what is his potency
彼はまた、自分の能力を採用するだろう
Do you think that these antibiotics are really magic medicines after seeing these effects?
これらの効果を見て、これらの抗生物質は本当に魔法の薬だと思いますか?
So when I was a kid I thought antibiotics were really the magic drug
だから子供の頃、抗生物質は本当に魔法の薬だと思っていました
Because it can treat many diseases
多くの病気を治療できるので、
lots of bacterial infections
細菌感染症が多い
Whether you are accidentally tired today
今日はうっかり疲れていても
and you have a hole in your leg
そしてあなたの足には穴があります
And then accidentally turned into a bacterial infection
そして誤って細菌感染症になってしまう
Whether you have any bacterial infection
細菌感染症があるかどうか
I just need a little antibiotic
少し抗生物質が必要なだけです
This wound will heal and it won't continue to thicken.
この傷は治りますし、それ以上厚くなることはありません。
I believe everyone has this experience
誰もがそんな経験があると思います
what this experience brings
この経験がもたらすもの
Here's some interesting news I stumbled from the internet
インターネットで偶然見つけた興味深いニュースをご紹介します
Antibiotic Resistance Deaths from Antibiotic Resistance
抗生物質耐性 抗生物質耐性による死亡数
For example, on February 3, 2017
たとえば、2017 年 2 月 3 日の場合
I'm talking about hygrobacteria
湿潤菌について話しているのですが
Hungry hygrobacterium turns into a superbug
飢えた湿性細菌がスーパーバグに変身
Antibiotic resistance may develop
抗生物質耐性が発生する可能性がある
It turned out to be in 2050
2050年になっていることが判明
Died of antibiotic resistance
抗生物質耐性で死亡
There are about 4.7 million people in Asia
アジアには約470万人がいます
Now that's not me too sensational
それは私にとってそれほどセンセーショナルではありません
Everyone may still live here
誰もがまだここに住んでいるかもしれない
Everyone is very healthy
みんなとても健康です
no cough
咳はありません
and no pain
そして痛みはありません
So everyone thinks that the drug resistance is far away from me.
そのため、薬剤耐性は私には縁遠いものだと誰もが思っています。
That's not my business
それは私の仕事ではありません
But it appears in all the data
しかし、それはすべてのデータに現れます
wait a minute i'll tell you something
ちょっと待ってください、何か言います
Finally I have an era
ついに私にも時代が来た
I will tell you guys that a recent post was interesting
最近の投稿が面白かったのでお知らせします
your puppy
あなたの子犬
inside dog poop
犬のうんちの中
0.6%
0.6%
Xu Xun production containing drug resistance
薬物耐性を含む徐迅の生産
wait a minute i'll let you know
ちょっと待ってください、お知らせします
What a terrible thing drug-resistant Xu Xun is
薬物耐性のある徐迅はなんと恐ろしいことだろう
Although now we still have a magic medicine to cure us
今はまだ私たちを治す魔法の薬があるのに
But will there be no magic medicine to save us in the future?
しかし、将来私たちを救う特効薬は存在しないのでしょうか？
Will there be other alternatives to replace antibiotics?
抗生物質に代わる他の代替薬はあるのでしょうか?
This is the first question we want to ask
これが私たちが尋ねたい最初の質問です
can report to everyone
みんなに報告できる
Indiscriminate use of antimicrobial bacteria in the prelude is becoming more and more serious
前兆における抗菌細菌の無差別使用はますます深刻になっている
So human beings' practical meat is centrally victimized
つまり、人間の実用的な肉が中心的に犠牲になっているのです
This is an article published on the news in 2015
2015年のニュースに掲載された記事です
There was a funny thing when I was a kid
子供の頃に面白い事があった
Because when I was a child, my family had pigs
子供の頃、実家で豚を飼っていたので、
i remember as long as i can remember
覚えている限り覚えています
because my father worked in a sugar factory
私の父は製糖工場で働いていたので、
So the income from working in the sugar factory should not be very high
したがって、製糖工場で働くことによる収入はそれほど高くないはずです
So my dad helped raise the pigs
それで父は豚の飼育を手伝いました
We have pigs next door to our house
私たちの家族は家のすぐ隣で豚を飼っています
next to our house
私たちの家の隣に
I remember when I was a child there was a thing called Orofi
私が子供の頃、オロフィというものがあったことを覚えています
Roof
屋根
do you all know
皆さんは知っていますか
It can be seen that we are about the same age
同じくらいの年齢であることがわかります
This Orofi is fun
このオロフィは楽しいです
everyone should know
誰もが知っておくべきです
Sometimes kids don't eat
子どもが食べないこともあります
or eating fatter
または太ったものを食べる
You eat Orofi big
オロフィを大きく食べるね
we were like this when we were kids
僕らは子供の頃こうだった
When I was in elementary school, sometimes my friends would say
小学生の頃、友達に時々言われました。
You eat Orofi
オロフィを食べる
Later, when I grew up, I found out
その後、大人になってから知りましたが、
Olby is not such an interesting thing
オルビーはそんなに面白いものではない
why olby
なぜオルビーなのか
What about Alfa?
アルファはどうですか？
It is an additive to medicated feed
薬用飼料への添加物です
At the same time, he was the section chief of Huangjianyu Drug Management Section in Ouerhui
同時に、黄建宇薬品管理課の課長
Xian Zhongfa pointed out
Xian Zhonfa氏は指摘した。
It is an antibiotic that has been added to the feed in low amounts for a long time
長期間にわたり飼料に少量添加されてきた抗生物質です。
It is easy to make the bacteria in the intestinal tract of animals resistant to antibiotics
動物の腸内細菌は抗生物質に対して耐性を持ちやすくなる
this troublesome one
この面倒なやつ
It Olbi was originally created to heal
オルビはもともと治癒のために作られました
for the treatment of bacterial infections
細菌感染症の治療用
Because pigs stand up easily
豚は立ちやすいから
It is during the pig's growth period
豚の成長期です
it is easy to stand
立つのは簡単です
Then there will be a bacterial infection causing it to stand down
その後、細菌感染が起こり、機能が停止します
At this time, drug-resistant bacteria will develop
このとき、薬剤耐性菌が発生します。
So if you are using low volume
したがって、小さな音量を使用している場合は、
Then the long-term low volume has been
その後、長期にわたる低生産量が続いています。
What will be added to the feed
フィードに追加されるもの
produce resistant bacteria
耐性菌を生み出す
The other one is the National Institutes of Health
もう一つは国立衛生研究所です。
his sui researcher
彼の水の研究者
Specific Researcher also speaks
特定の研究者も講演
In fact, our animal husbandry uses antibiotics indiscriminately
実際、私たちの畜産現場では抗生物質が無差別に使用されています。
meat safety
肉の安全性
Maybe it will follow the black heart
たぶんそれは黒い心を追うでしょう
Taiwan three
台湾三
a big real question
大きな本当の質問
Wait a minute and I will too
ちょっと待ってください、私もそうします
I will also report to you
またご報告させていただきます
Don't talk about Taiwan
台湾のことは話すな
Let me report to everyone, I think the situation in mainland China is more troublesome than yours
皆さんに報告させてください、中国本土の状況はあなたたちの状況よりもさらに厄介だと思います
Mainland I believe they don't use antibiotics
本土では抗生物質は使われていないと思います
mainland pork
本土の豚肉
Pork in mainland China until now
これまでの中国本土の豚肉
some are imported
一部は輸入されています
Because some of them raise pigs in the country
田舎で豚を飼っている人もいるから
Information on antibiotics may also be used
抗生物質に関する情報も使用される場合があります
I think antibiotics are in mainland China
抗生物質は中国本土にあると思う
in Taiwan or in Southeast Asian countries
台湾や東南アジア諸国では
Cases that should abound
豊富にあるべきケース
then let's talk about it
それからそれについて話しましょう
antibiotic
抗生素的
Why These Bacteria Become Drug-Resistant
なぜこれらの細菌が薬剤耐性を持つようになるのか
Because for example, this is a very simple
なぜなら、これは非常に単純な例だからです。
From a very simple graph
非常に単純なグラフから
Because this bacterium if
なぜなら、この細菌が
If the bacteria become resistant
菌が耐性を持ってしまうと
it goes through beef cattle or pigs or chickens
肉牛、豚、鶏を経由する
after eating
食べた後で
It's antibiotics, it can't kill the bacteria with the yellow dot
それは抗生物質ですが、黄色い点のある細菌を殺すことはできません
So this resistant bacterium
つまりこの耐性菌は
still remain in
まだ残っている
then it passes through feces
その後、糞便を通過します
if there is any food
食べ物があれば
You can eat it later
後で食べてもいいよ
After people step on these resolutions or implement
人々がこれらの決議を実行または実行した後、
the drug-resistant bacteria with these yellow dots
この黄色い点のある薬剤耐性菌
remain in the human body
人の体内に残る
So what kind of impact does this have? Is it sick?
では、これはどのような影響を与えるのでしょうか?病気なのでしょうか?
So when a bacterial infection
したがって、細菌感染症が起こると、
When we humans have so-called drug-resistant bacterial infections
私たち人間がいわゆる薬剤耐性菌感染症にかかると、
On the back of the medical treatment on the clinical
臨床上の医療の裏側に
is very tricky
とても難しいです
Especially in doctors they have to prescribe some appropriate antibiotics
特に医師の場合は、適切な抗生物質を処方しなければなりません。
when appropriate antibiotics
適切な場合は抗生物質
It's actually very, very tricky.
それは実際にはとてもとても難しいことです。
When I want to tell you this list
このリストを伝えたいとき
This is called a post-antibiotic era
これはポスト抗生物質の時代と呼ばれます
In this book in 2013
2013年のこの本の中で
Tell us that green plum trees were born in 1928
青梅の誕生は1928年だと教えてください
Green plum tree is actually a very interesting story
青梅の木って実はとても面白い話なんです
The green plum tree is the stock crops raised in a pile
青梅の木は山積みに育てられた農作物です
It has a fungus that fell into it
中に菌が入ってます
Then he found that around the fungus
それから彼は菌類の周りにあることを発見しました
Every bacterium is surrounded by prison
あらゆる細菌を囲い込む
Then there is no inferior growth in the vicinity
そうすれば、近くに劣った成長はありません
Then after floating for a year, I feel
それから一年漂ってみて感じたのは、
it's a lot of fun
とても楽しいです
very interesting phenomenon
非常に興味深い現象
to develop a drug
薬を開発する
Then we can see that from 19%
そうすると、19% からそれがわかります。
From 1987 to the present, from 2011 to the present
1987年から現在まで、2011年から現在まで
We don't have so-called new antibiotics
いわゆる新しい抗生物質はありません
Until 2014, 2015
2014年、2015年まで
There is a drug that has been approved by the US FDA
アメリカのFDAに認可された薬がある
Approved for marketing, recently there is another antibiotic approved for marketing
販売が承認されました。最近、別の抗生物質が販売を承認されました。
so
それで
until so many years
何年も前まで
In fact, none of us have the so-called new antibiotics.
実際、いわゆる新しい抗生物質を持っている人は誰もいません。
The development of these antibiotics since the beginning of mankind
人類の始まり以来、これらの抗生物質の開発は
The period from 1928 to 1987 was the peak period of antibiotics
1928 年から 1987 年は抗生物質の最盛期でした。
When humans discovered these antibiotics
人類がこれらの抗生物質を発見したとき
Antibiotics are also booming most during this time
抗生物質もこの時期に最もブームになります
This period of time also created the history of human health
この時代は人類の健康の歴史も生み出しました
best brilliant stage
最高に輝かしいステージ
this stage
この段階
As soon as any anti-suspended bacteria come out, they will be eliminated by the following drugs
抗揮発性菌が出てきたら、以下の薬剤で即座に抑制します。
kill it
それを殺します
So you can see that in 1928, seven or eight years of antibiotics were produced, in 1945, four or five years of antibiotics were produced, and in 1979, another antibiotic was produced
つまり、1928 年には 7 ～ 8 年分の抗生物質が製造され、1945 年には 4 ～ 5 年分の抗生物質が製造され、1979 年には別の抗生物質が製造されたことがわかります。
these things
これらの事
Dongying suppressed the so-called
東営はいわゆる
broad-spectrum resistance
広範囲の耐性
Antibiotic Bacteria
抗生物質バクテリア
So what we're going to say next, this is what I just reported to you
それでは次にお話しするのは、これが先ほどあなたに報告した内容です
In 2014, naturally...
2014年には当然...
There is a journal called Nature Biotechnology
Nature Biotechnology という雑誌があります
One biotechnology inside Nature, one inside a journal
1 つのバイオテクノロジーは自然の中に、もう 1 つはジャーナルの中に
October 2014, it has an interesting story
2014 年 10 月、興味深い話がありました
A description, it says US FDA
説明にはUS FDAと書かれています
is what we know as the FDA
それは私たちがFDAとして知っていることです
It makes a drug, the drug can be approved for marketing
それは薬を製造し、その薬は販売を承認されることができます
This is a new type of antibiotic
これは新しいタイプの抗生物質です
It's presumably in IV mode, it hits the vein
おそらくIVモードで、静脈に当たります
Then prevent some of the bacteria that MSA infects
次に、MSA が感染する細菌の一部を防ぎます。
It's a troublesome bacterium, the bacterial infection of MSA
やっかいな菌です、MSAの細菌感染症
At the same time, a year earlier, in 2013,
同時に、その 1 年前の 2013 年には、
Someone started talking about antimicrobial status coming back
誰かが抗菌ステータスが戻ってきたことについて話し始めました
Should we be looking for a new anti...
新しいアンチを探したほうがいいでしょうか...
an antibacterial substance other than antibiotics
抗生物質以外の抗菌物質
So in the 2013 Nature Journal of Biotechnology in the Nature Journal
そこで、Nature Journal の 2013 Nature Journal of Biotechnology で
He mentioned a report that said
彼は次のような報告書について言及した。
Antibacterial
抗菌
Come back and do some research
帰ってきて調べてみる
Is it possible as a new type of
新しいタイプとしては可能でしょうか？
new antimicrobial substances
新しい抗菌物質
Therefore, the antibacterial state research has probably been
したがって、抗菌状態の研究はおそらく
twenty years, twenty or thirty years
二十年、二十年か三十年
Probably more intensive research
おそらくより集中的な研究が行われるでしょう
There are now more than 350,000 papers
現在、論文数は 350,000 を超えています
are published in some related journals
いくつかの関連雑誌に掲載されています
so we feel
だから私たちは感じます
We just reported to you
先ほどご報告させていただきました
there are many struggles
多くの葛藤があります
the consequences of the impact
影響の結果
leads us to want to find a new
新しいものを見つけたいと思うようになります
substance that replaces the number of struggles
闘いの数に代わる物質
Otherwise, there will be no medicine for human beings in the future
そうしないと将来人間に効く薬がなくなってしまいます
when there is no medical treatment
治療法がないとき
And with that comes a lot of death
そしてそれには多くの死が伴います
as the epic of yan said
ヤンの叙事詩が言ったように
Birth of the Black Death
黒死病の誕生
on top of some of the history we know
私たちが知っている歴史の一部に加えて
Alright, so we're going to report to you
さて、それではご報告させていただきます
what is antibacterial state
抗菌状態とは何ですか
The origin of the antibacterial state is actually what I just reported to you
抗菌状態の起源は、実は先ほどお伝えしたことなのです
In 1928, the so-called panlucillin was produced
1928年にいわゆるパンルシリンが製造されました。
In 1939 there was the so-called
1939 年にいわゆる
Production of short-susceptible bacterium
短感受性細菌の生産
In the 1950s, everyone had the so-called anti-halo
1950年代には、誰もがいわゆるアンチハローを持っていました
Some people began to discover the so-called anti-halo state
いわゆるアンチハロー状態を発見し始めた人もいる
So far we probably know
今まではおそらく知っています
Antibiotics that may appear to be able to replace antibiotics
抗生物質の代わりになりそうな抗生物質
is able to serve as a cancer treatment drug
がん治療薬として機能することができます
The latest research results
最新の研究結果
we haven't
私たちはしていない
We only have some verification on the so-called animal experiments
いわゆる動物実験については若干の検証しかありません。
But we believe in the future of halo resistance
しかし、私たちはハロー耐性の未来を信じています
Appears to be a replacement for antibiotics
抗生物質の代替品になるようです
a new substance
新しい物質
Next I will talk about some of our laboratory
次に私たちの研究室についてお話します。
Report the results of the research and development
研究開発の成果を報告します
Why Antisickness Could Be an Emerging Drug in the Future
なぜ抗酔い薬が将来の新薬となる可能性があるのか
Why anti-halostates have the power to replace antibiotics
抗ハロゲン化物質が抗生物質に代わる力を持つ理由
Why anti-halostate may be used as an emerging anti-cancer drug in the future
抗ハロステート剤が将来新たな抗がん剤として使用される可能性がある理由
you probably don't know
あなたはおそらく知らないでしょう
One of the newest emerging cancer drugs is called PDL1
最新の抗がん剤の 1 つは PDL1 と呼ばれます
PDL1 I just recently found out
PDL1 最近知った
it is a very expensive drug
それはとても高価な薬です
A course of treatment should be done 24 times
1コースの治療は24回行う必要があります
For each course of treatment, do you want to guess how many times it has?
各治療コースの回数を推測しますか?
244 after a course of treatment
244 一連の治療後
you probably know
あなたはおそらく知っています
PDL1 this latest
この最新の PDL1
anticancer drugs
抗がん剤
Do you know how much it costs?
どれくらいの費用がかかるか知っていますか？
Nope
いいえ
I only recently found out
つい最近知ったのですが
3000000
3000000
right
右
I
私
I'm scared to death
死ぬほど怖いです
I was scared to death when I heard that number
その数字を聞いたとき死ぬほど怖かった
so why do we want
それでなぜ私たちは欲しいのですか
Want to find an up-to-date drug production
最新の医薬品生産を知りたい
just hope we will
そうなるように願っています
we can in taiwan
台湾でもできるよ
find out find out from deep water creatures
深海生物から調べる
Our own Niche in Taiwan
台湾における当社独自のニッチ市場
You see, Taiwan is surrounded by the sea
台湾は海に囲まれているので、
So Taiwan's marine biotechnology research
台湾の海洋バイオテクノロジー研究
Won't
しません
will not alienate other countries
他国を疎外しない
We should pay more attention to the marine life
私たちは海洋生物にもっと注意を払うべきです
get the natural resources we need
必要な天然資源を手に入れる
then later
じゃあ後で
Transform back to what we want to introduce to you
私たちが紹介したいものに戻ります
anti-pregnancy
妊娠防止
Anti-pregnancy is actually basically it
反妊娠は実際には基本的にそれです
Probably divided into several types in terms of shape
おそらく形状からいくつかのタイプに分かれる
Then its type has the so-called spiral
そのタイプはいわゆるスパイラルです
Or a shape similar to a board
または板に似た形状
or a shape with specific amino acids
または特定のアミノ酸を含む形状
That's one of the anti-rhyme patterns we listed.
これは、私たちがリストした韻を踏まないパターンの 1 つです。
That anti-rhyme, it will have plants and animals in all animals
その反韻、あらゆる動物に植物と動物が含まれます
including in your body
あなたの体の中にも含めて
The human body also has the so-called anti-rhyme fetus
人間の体にも、いわゆる「反韻胎児」が備わっています。
There is a so-called anti-rhyme tire in the body of the fish
魚の体にはいわゆるアンチライムタイヤが付いています。
The anti-rhyme substance is like the eggs you have eaten
反韻物質はあなたが食べた卵のようなものです
You all know that eggs contain a lot of protein, right?
卵にはたんぱく質が多く含まれていることは皆さんご存知ですよね？
But the ecology is relatively small
しかし生態系は比較的小さい
small molecules smaller than proteins
タンパク質よりも小さい小分子
Only about 20 amino acids to 50 amino acids
わずか20アミノ酸から50アミノ酸程度
Smaller anti-rhyme tires are now reported
小型のアンチライムタイヤが報告されています
About 5 to 10 amino acids have antibacterial ability
抗菌力を持つアミノ酸は5～10個程度
So our family just reported that
それで私たちの家族はちょうどそれを報告しました
Anti-rhyme tires actually exist in all nature
アンチライムタイヤは実際に自然界に存在します
Including puppies and cats in your home
あなたの家の子犬や猫も含めて
piggy too
豚も
Okay, let's also tell you about anti-rhythm tires, which can kill a lot of bacteria.
さて、多くのバクテリアを殺すことができるアンチリズムタイヤについてもお話しましょう。
It can be verified experimentally
実験的に検証できる
Anti rhyme can kill bacteria
アンチライムは細菌を殺すことができる
Needles, protozoa, and cancer
針、原虫、がん
It can also have what is called immune regulation
いわゆる免疫調節機能を持つこともあります
wait a minute i tell you
ちょっと待ってください、私が言います
You all may not know one thing
皆さんも知らないことがあるかもしれません
maybe know something
もしかしたら何かを知っているかもしれない
when we catch a cold
私たちが風邪をひいたとき
When we have a bacterial infection when we are injured
怪我をしたとき、細菌感染症にかかったとき
you will hurt, right?
傷つきますよね？
Will everyone be in pain?
みんなも痛むのかな？
like sometimes when my mother is sick
時々母が病気のときのように
very painful
とても痛い
Tell me every day that she has back pain
彼女は背中が痛いと毎日言ってください
or which side hurts
それともどちら側が痛いのか
do you know why it hurts
なぜ痛いか知っていますか
Pain is due to bacterial infection
痛みは細菌感染によるものです
Cause immune inflammation, increase immune factors
免疫炎症を引き起こし、免疫因子を強化する
but you know
しかし、あなたは知っています
you bring
あなたが持ってくる
Sometimes we most often hear a sentence that is
時々、私たちは次のような文をよく聞きます。
The child goes to the hospital
子供が病院に行く
what is a good doctor
良い医者とは何ですか
A good doctor is to prevent children from crying
良い医者は子供を泣かせないようにすることである
Take an iron medicine now
今すぐ鉄剤を飲みましょう
take medicine for a day
一日薬を飲む
The grandson won't cry if he hugs him back
孫は抱きしめ返しても泣かない
Then grandpa and grandma said
すると、おじいちゃんとおばあちゃんが言いました。
this doctor give me doctor
この医者は私に医者を与えます
so that's not going to be good
だからそれは良くないよ
is it interesting
面白いですか
yes it's interesting let me tell you
はい、興味深いです、教えてください
now have some medicine
今、薬を持ってきてください
so-called steroids
いわゆるステロイド
What are steroid drugs for?
ステロイド薬は何のためにあるのですか？
some steroid medicines
いくつかのステロイド薬
It suppresses your immune inflammatory response
免疫炎症反応を抑制します
when our human body
私たちの人間の体が
When we humans suffer from bacterial infection
私たち人間が細菌感染症にかかると、
The most likely to happen is the immune system
最も起こりやすいのは免疫システムです
it will start to raise
上がり始めるだろう
The immune system seems to have some immune genes
免疫システムにはいくつかの免疫遺伝子があるようです
Will be sequenced to produce some cytokines
いくつかのサイトカインを生成するために配列決定される予定
or the production of immune factors
または免疫因子の生成
It's time to induce your body
あなたの体を誘導する時間です
giant cells or intermediate leukocytes
巨細胞または中間白血球
to phagocytize the bacteria washed in
洗った細菌を貪食する
But sometimes a good doctor
でも時々良い医者もいる
Of course, there are fewer such good doctors now.
もちろん、今ではそのような優秀な医師は少なくなりました。
I guess again
またそうだね
But because of the request of the family
でも家族の要望もあって
Grandpa and grandma's request or parent's request
おじいちゃん、おばあちゃんのリクエストや両親のリクエスト
Said that today I grow very thin
今日はすごく痩せたって言ってた
i slept all day in my sister ok
私は妹の中で一日中寝ました、わかりました
This doctor is better
この医者の方が良い
After taking the medicine for a day, my sister will not be well
薬を一日飲んだ後、妹の体調が悪くなります
so this doctor is good
だからこの医者は良いよ
He gave you some steroids
彼はあなたにステロイドを与えました
Steroids reduce pain
ステロイドは痛みを軽減します
it's very good, but i feel like i have to say
とても良いけど、話してしまいそうな気がする
Steroids are the magic drug I've known since
ステロイドは私が昔から知っている魔法の薬です
other than antibiotics
抗生物質以外の
it keeps you from pain
それはあなたを痛みから守ります
Then do you know that every system is reduced
それでは、あらゆるシステムが縮小されていることをご存知ですか
For example, when your original bacteria are cleaned
たとえば、元のバクテリアが浄化されると、
There are giant bubbles with four intermediate white bacteria
巨大な泡があり、中間の白いバクテリアが 4 つあります
It's going to devour the bacteria in your light body
それはあなたのライトボディのバクテリアを食べるでしょう
As a result, each system has a reduced
その結果、各システムのコストが削減されます。
it suppresses your immunity
それはあなたの免疫力を抑制します
What does that bring?
それは何をもたらすのでしょうか？
what about these bacteria
これらの細菌はどうですか
flourishing
繁栄している
Because there is no army to kill these bacteria
なぜなら、これらの細菌を殺すための軍隊がないからです。
that without killing
それは殺さずに
Bacteria are of course happy to produce
もちろんバクテリアは喜んで生産します
Then the doctor will definitely use
そうすれば医者は間違いなく使うでしょう
How many things are prescribed in your medicine
あなたの薬には何種類のものが処方されていますか
antibiotic
抗生素
It's two sides of the same thing, right?
それは同じことの裏表ですよね？
You have suppressed your immunity
免疫力を抑制してしまった
Bacteria proliferate
細菌が増殖する
Then this person won't hang you up
そうすれば、この人は電話を切らないでしょう
You say it's possible or impossible?
それは可能だと思いますか、不可能だと思いますか？
when bacteria are about to go up
菌が増えそうなとき
It gives you antibiotics to kill the bacteria
細菌を殺すために抗生物質を投与します
So basically in many drugs
基本的に多くの薬では
The doctor will prescribe these two drugs together
医師はこれら 2 つの薬を一緒に処方します
Let you not be in pain and get well again
痛みを感じずにまた元気になれますように
so it's a vicious cycle
だから悪循環だよ
Begins to generate endless nightmares
終わりのない悪夢を生み出し始める
I want to report to everyone that is
ということを皆さんにご報告したいと思います
fighting it has an advantage
戦うのが有利だ
It inhibits the production of some inflammatory factors
いくつかの炎症因子の生成を抑制します
So it has what's called immune regulation
つまり、免疫調節と呼ばれるものがあるのです
But it also has the ability to kill bacteria
しかし細菌を殺す力もあります
Unlike what I just reported to you
先ほどご報告した内容とは異なります
You must take two medicines
薬を2つ服用しなければなりません
Now if it can really become medicine
これで本当に薬になれるなら
You only need to eat one
1つだけ食べればいいよ
wait a minute you will ask me
ちょっと待ってください、あなたは私に尋ねます
Is there any resistance to anti-morbidity?
抗罹患率に対する耐性はありますか?
i will tell you
言いますよ
Is there a question of drug resistance?
薬剤耐性の問題はありますか?
So everyone should be curious and ask me
だからみんなも興味を持って私に聞いてください
until now
今まで
Has the world's anti-morbidity been made into medicine?
世界の抗疾患薬は医学化されていますか?
Because I saw someone on B said
Bで誰かが言ってたのを見たからだ
Has this medicine come out?
この薬は切れていますか？
Is there any medicine
薬はありますか
Who is this shoot
この撮影者は誰ですか
There is not yet any anti-morbid drug
抗病性薬はまだありません
have been used clinically
臨床で使用されています
be industrialized commercialized
工業化される
but there are many drugs
でも薬はたくさんある
Has entered clinical phase II or III
臨床第 II 相または第 III 相に入っている
even like this drug is done
この薬が終わったように
That's for diabetes
それは糖尿病用です
What about diabetic patients?
糖尿病患者についてはどうですか？
he sometimes has wounds
彼は時々傷を負っている
big wound
大きな傷
Because everyone is still full
まだみんなお腹いっぱいだから
So I'm sticking that picture over here
だからその写真をここに貼っておきます
Everyone is interested to see
誰もが興味を持って見ています
i don't want to put that picture
その写真は載せたくない
Wait a minute everyone is throwing up over here
ちょっと待って、みんなここで吐いてるよ
What about the other one?
もう一つはどうですか？
and catheter
そしてカテーテル
You may not have experience
経験がないかもしれません
It hurts to eat that catheter
そのカテーテルを食べると痛いです
But sometimes when the catheter is full, the urine bag comes out
ただし、カテーテルがいっぱいになると、尿バッグが出てくることがあります。
when urine flushes back
尿が逆流するとき
It's easy to get bacteria over there
そこに細菌が入りやすい
So what about the catheter thing?
では、カテーテルの場合はどうでしょうか？
Many people have been making anti-smoke soup
多くの人が禁煙スープを作っています
and then do some
それから何かをしてください
in some
いくつかでは
put some anti-smoke soup on the catheter
カテーテルに禁煙スープを付けます
make it sterilizable
滅菌できるようにする
Candida infection
カンジダ感染症
for example
例えば
sometimes
時々
Your mouth and tongue will be white
口も舌も真っ白になりますよ
that resembles a bacterial infection
細菌感染症に似ている
Then everyone can brush it out with any toothbrush
そうすれば、誰でも歯ブラシでそれを磨くことができます
mouth smelly today
今日は口が臭い
Because the teeth are not brushed well
歯磨きがしっかりできていないため
But in fact, after brushing it ten times and twenty times, it still smells bad.
しかし、実際には10回、20回磨いても臭いが残ります。
because there is no mobile phone
携帯電話がないので
It's sort of a pregnancy infection because the white layer is over there
あそこに白い層があるので、妊娠感染症のようなものです
This is the so-called roller fungus infection, so some people put the anti-smoke form in the empty water for brushing their teeth before doing research and development.
これはいわゆるローラー菌感染症なので、研究開発を行う前に歯磨き用の空の水に禁煙剤を入れる人もいます。
All kinds of these anti-smoke states are in the data we compiled in 2015, we probably know that there are these anti-smoke states
これらのあらゆる種類の禁煙州は、2015 年に私たちがまとめたデータに含まれており、おそらくこれらの禁煙州が存在することはわかっています。
Has entered clinical phase II and phase III or has even ended
臨床第 II 相および第 III 相に入ったか、または終了したことさえある
I was in our firm last year, and every year there are so-called PI speeches in our firm
私は昨年私たちの事務所にいましたが、毎年私たちの事務所ではいわゆるPIスピーチが行われます。
I will talk to us about the report in the same text. The research I did is that Sus mother has been herding sheep for 18 years.
この報告書については同じ文章でお話ししますが、私が行った調査によると、スーさんの母親は 18 年間羊飼いをしていました。
Why shepherd sheep for 18 years, I will report to all of you later
なぜ18年間も羊飼いをしているのか、また後日皆さんにご報告します
Like this drug is 1998 in Joc this drug, this drug is this drug
この薬は Joc では 1998 年であるように、この薬はこの薬です、この薬はこの薬です
A drug from this company
この会社の薬
it uses an anti-smoke form as a drug
それは薬物として抗煙剤を使用します
Since it published this magazine in 1998
1998年にこの雑誌を創刊して以来、
everyone can see
誰もが見ることができます
until October 25, 2016
2016年10月25日まで
US APPDA
米国APPDA
It actually failed the clinical phase III test, because the US APPDA felt that its
米国のAPPDAは、実際には臨床第III相試験に合格しなかった。
The results of its measurements are not hot for the present
測定結果は今のところホットではない
Existing drugs for trauma have better outcomes
外傷に対する既存の薬はより良い結果をもたらす
more meaningful difference
もっと意味のある違い
So the DA in the United States rejected the drug body
そのため、米国の検事局は麻薬本体を拒否した
I told our comrades
私は仲間たちに言いました
It has been herding for 19 years
19年間にわたって放牧を続けている
I may have to keep me like this for more than 20 years
20年以上このままでいなきゃいけないかも
Because foreign funds may be more abundant
外国の資金がもっと潤沢にあるかもしれないから
We are in Taiwan and I have been looking for a pharmaceutical factory to cooperate with
私たちは台湾におり、協力してくれる製薬工場を探しています。
Come and help us herd the sheep
羊の群れを手伝ってください
Then this chance of shepherding still hopes to have a chance in the future
そして、この羊飼いのチャンスは、将来的にもまだチャンスがあることを望んでいます
You can treat the whole world based on Taiwan
台湾を拠点に全世界を扱える
I've been lecturing to Pops, the student council assistant in our lab,
私は研究室の生徒会補佐のポップスに講義をしてきたのですが、
We are in Xiaosuo Taiwan
私たちは台湾の小蘇にいます
we want something like
私たちは次のようなものが欲しいです
When everyone talks about similarities, they talk about old similarities
誰もが類似点について話すとき、彼らは古い類似点について話します
speaking of chocolate
チョコレートといえば
in such a small country
こんな小さな国で
How can it develop such a famous thing
どうしたらこんな有名なものが開発できるのか
So we're doing research in the little territorial waters
そこで私たちは小さな領海で調査を行っています
We want to be able to make a world that can
できる世界を作りたいと願っています。
a thing used
使われた物
let me tell you now
今教えてください
antibacterial tire
抗菌タイヤ
what does it look like
それは何に見えますか
can let
させられる
Does not develop resistance like antibiotics
抗生物質のように耐性が生じない
This is a very important feature
これは非常に重要な機能です
no antibiotics
抗生物質なし
antibacterial tire
抗菌タイヤ
it will have so-called
いわゆる
that
それか
A break in the groove
溝の休憩
A Mechanism for Breaking Bacterial Cell Membranes
細菌の細胞膜を破壊するメカニズム
For example it has what's called a vat side panel pattern
たとえば、バットサイドパネルパターンと呼ばれるものがあります。
This is antibacterial tire
抗菌タイヤです
It is antibacterial on the surface of bacterial cell B or cell membrane
細菌細胞Bまたは細胞膜の表面で抗菌性を示します。
It will utilize a schema like this big bucket
この大きなバケツのようなスキーマを利用します
Then insert it into the bacterial cell B or above the cell membrane
次に、細菌細胞Bまたは細胞膜の上に挿入します。
become a hole
穴になる
Then the contents of the bacteria will flow out
そうすると菌の中身が流れ出てきます
Then the bacteria die
そうすれば細菌は死滅します
The other is the carpet pattern
もう一つはカーペットの柄です
I can only talk about these two very simple modes today
今日はこれら 2 つの非常に単純なモードについてしか話せません
Then these two modes will let the bacteria hang
次に、これら 2 つのモードでバクテリアをぶら下げます。
It's going to be a lot of fun on the web
ウェブ上ではとても楽しいことになるでしょう
very interesting video
とても興味深いビデオ
I'll let everyone take a look
みんなに見てもらいましょう
because
なぜなら
this
これ
This is the one on YouTube
これはYouTubeにあるものです
an interesting Data
興味深いデータ
You can see it's bacteria
細菌であることがわかります
Then it starts to be antibacterial on the connection
その後、接続部分で抗菌が始まります
It will break the chain, break the determination, break some troubles
それは鎖を断ち切り、決意を断ち切り、いくつかのトラブルを断ち切るでしょう
burst the bacteria
細菌を破裂させる
You can see this green thing forming a hole
この緑色のものが穴を形成しているのがわかります
Then the bacteria stuff comes out
そうするとバクテリアが出てくるんです
Then the bacteria disintegrates
そうするとバクテリアが分解される
these disintegrating things
これらの崩壊するもの
Bacteria will no longer increase in value
バクテリアの価値が上がらなくなります
no more harm to the human body
もう人体に害はありません
So after we finish talking about this
それで、この話が終わったら
Everyone must be curious and ask me
誰もが興味を持って私に尋ねるはずです
Teacher Chen, just now I was wondering if you are doing well
チェン先生、今、元気かなぁと思ってたんですが
Let's look at the next
次を見てみましょう
This is the hospital cooperation published by PNS in 2014
これは 2014 年に PNS によって発行された病院協力です。
You can see it when doing PM
PMをするときに見ることができます
electron microscope
電子顕微鏡
You can see this is a beautiful bacillus
これは美しい桿菌であることがわかります
Bacillus it passes through an antibacterial tire
抗菌タイヤを通過するバチルス
It's called C3A, use 0.3 micron
C3Aと呼ばれるもので、0.3ミクロンを使用します
It can burst the bacteria
細菌を破壊する可能性があります
This is what a Streptococcus pneumoniae does in our lab
これが私たちの研究室での肺炎球菌の活動です
You can see that pneumococcus is beautiful
肺炎球菌が綺麗なのがわかりますね
like a basketball
バスケットボールのように
We also see these bacteria
こんな細菌も見られます
I really think the recruiter is really good at recruiting
採用担当者は本当に採用が上手だと思う
This is handsome eyebrow feather
こちらはイケメン眉毛です
The handsome eyebrows in this bacteria
この細菌のハンサムな眉毛
But many doctors in infection department saw this
しかし、感染症科の多くの医師はこれを目にしました
Everyone is scared to death
みんな死ぬほど怖いよ
How could so much of this thing be detected in the patient's blood
どうして患者の血液からこれほど多くの物質が検出されたのでしょうか
After we added the antibacterial status of the grouper
ハタの抗菌ステータスを追加した後
You can see the bacteria disintegrate all over it
バクテリアがあちこちで分解されているのがわかります
This is the result of an experiment we did in 2005
これは 2005 年に行った実験の結果です
Streptococcus pneumoniae is a troublesome disease
肺炎球菌は厄介な病気です
another one
もう一つ
This is the so-called vaginal petting
いわゆる膣ペッティングです
This is a gene bank bought vagina low pet bought by ATCC
これは遺伝子バンクがATCCによって購入された膣の低いペットです
This is a low favor of the vagina obtained from the clinic
これはクリニックから得た膣の低い好意です
Vaginal low pampering can cause many unpleasant ailments for the wealthy
膣の甘やかしが少ないと、裕福な人に多くの不快な病気を引き起こす可能性があります
If we put antibacterial status together with these vagina pets
これらの膣ペットと抗菌ステータスを組み合わせると
You can see that this treatment of the grouper just talked to it
このハタの扱いは、ハタに話しかけただけであることがわかります
1 in 10 is disease-resistant
10人に1人が病気に強い
We fight disease by using ecosynthesis
私たちは生態合成を利用して病気と闘います
The anti-pathological effect of a synthesized section of twenty-one amino acid
21個のアミノ酸の合成部分の抗病理学的効果
instead of putting the whole fish down
魚全体を下に置くのではなく
Don't get me wrong
誤解しないでください
After we put this synthetic anti-morbidity in
この合成抗罹患性物質を導入した後、
You can see nine hundred and sixty minutes later
960分後が見えます
The whole bacteria is disintegrated
細菌全体が分解される
This is the anti-morbidity obtained from the shrimp
これはエビから得られる抗疾病効果です
It also has the same function
こちらも同様の機能を搭載しております
Why Vaginal Lows Are Trouble Doing
なぜ膣の低音がうまくいかないのか
because it has a tick on the side
側面にカチカチが入っているので
It hooks the cell surface of the vaginal epithelium
膣上皮の細胞表面に引っ掛かります
So the disease will be cleaned repeatedly
それで病気は繰り返し浄化されるでしょう
Also because of its low vaginal weight, it has so-called drug resistance
また、膣の重量が少ないため、いわゆる薬剤耐性があります。
Many diseases are like flu
多くの病気はインフルエンザに似ています
ate it now the drug is a so-called
今食べました、その薬はいわゆる
Metadolol Anti-Correction into Coatings
メタドロールのコーティングへの修正防止剤
After treatment it will become a negative recurrence
治療後は陰性再発となる
well , we can know anti - pathological
まあ、私たちは抗病理学的を知ることができます
it kills these germs or something
それはこれらの細菌か何かを殺します
This is what I just reported to you
これが先ほどあなたに報告した内容です
anti-pathological it has the ability to inhibit some
抗病理学的、それは何らかのものを阻害する能力があります
suppression of immune inflammation
免疫炎症の抑制
an effect of a factor
要因の影響
Let's take a look
見てみましょう
It TLR method is a
TLR方式とは、
It is a factor of inflammation immunity
炎症免疫の要因です
When the car reaches this factor in the body
車がボディのこの要素に達すると
When this cell technology is manifested in large quantities
この細胞技術が大量に発現すると
It's kind of like an inflammation in the body.
体内で炎症が起きているようなものです。
That's when I just said
そのとき私はこう言いました
steroids or other drugs
ステロイドまたは他の薬
it can suppress this
これを抑制できる
The same antibacterial state can also inhibit it
同じ抗菌状態でもそれを阻害することができます
what's the other interesting thing
他に面白いことは何ですか
Antibacterial state it can act like an antibiotic
抗菌状態は抗生物質のように作用します
Many antibiotics go into bacteria
多くの抗生物質は細菌に作用します
It inhibits DNA to RNA
DNAからRNAへの変換を阻害します
or RNA into the process of protein synthesis
またはRNAをタンパク質合成のプロセスに導入
The same antibacterial state will
同じ抗菌状態が維持されます。
In 2011 this magazine told us that
2011年にこの雑誌が私たちにこう伝えました。
Antibacterial states There are many different antibacterial states
抗菌状態 抗菌状態にはさまざまな種類があります
For example, let me take one
たとえば、一つ挙げてみましょう
Here's an antibacterial state from that flounder
そのヒラメの抗菌状態がこちら
This antibacterial state it can inhibit DNA to protein
この抗菌状態は、DNAからタンパク質への変換を阻害することができます。
Bacterial DNA to protein synthesis
細菌の DNA からタンパク質への合成
So now there are some studies from here
それで今、ここからいくつかの研究があります
Reporting Research in the Lab
研究室での研究の報告
Tell us that the antimicrobial state has the potential to develop resistance
抗菌状態では耐性が発生する可能性があると教えてください
Currently there are some reports telling us
現在、いくつかの報告があります。
But it's all so-called artificially made in the laboratory.
しかし、それはすべて研究室でいわゆる人工的に作られたものです。
The so-called drug resistance has not been obtained in nature
いわゆる薬剤耐性は自然界では得られていない
antimicrobial resistance of a bacterium
細菌の抗菌剤耐性
Then I will report another phenomenon to you next.
それでは次にまた別の現象を報告させていただきます。
Just now everyone will see what I just said
今、私が今言ったことをみんなが見るでしょう
Bacterial infection will eventually cause what systemic
細菌感染は最終的には全身的な症状を引き起こします。
syndrome of inflammatory response
炎症反応症候群
so-called sepsis
いわゆる敗血症
Then many times the virus you are in the hospital
その後、ウイルスによって何度も入院することになります
You will all know the so-called sepsis
皆さんはいわゆる敗血症をご存知でしょう
The source of many of his infections is mostly bacteria.
彼の感染症の原因の多くは細菌です。
It may also be caused by fungal viruses or gauges to produce mild in vivo
また、真菌ウイルスや生体内で軽度の症状を引き起こすゲージによって引き起こされることもあります。
causing sepsis
敗血症を引き起こす
That sepsis is very troublesome, that is to say
敗血症は非常に厄介です、つまり
The trouble now is to say
今の問題は、言うことです
When he screened out some kind of resistant bacteria
ある種の耐性菌をスクリーニングしたとき
When there were no antibiotics to treat
治療のための抗生物質がなかった時代
This is the most troublesome place
ここが一番面倒なところです
He would treat patients with different antibiotics over and over again.
彼は患者をさまざまな抗生物質で何度も治療しました。
Of course there's no way it's going to cause what's called lung congestion.
もちろん、いわゆる肺うっ血を引き起こす可能性はありません。
then cause death
それから死を引き起こす
What about the anti... this sepsis?
抗...この敗血症についてはどうですか？
What about sepsis?
敗血症についてはどうですか？
Approximately 30% mortality
死亡率は約30％
Then the mortality rate of severe sepsis is about 50%.
そうすると、重篤な敗血症の死亡率は約50％になります。
Of course it varies with age.
もちろん年齢によっても異なります。
Sepsis Caused by Different Ethnic Groups and Different Regions
異なる民族および異なる地域によって引き起こされる敗血症
while the death rate varies
死亡率は変動するものの
we must tell you now
今すぐ言わなければなりません
This... is the current treatment in medicine
これが現在の医学の治療法です
that's what i just told you
それが私が今言ったことです
anticancer drugs
抗がん剤
What about the anticancer drug?
抗がん剤はどうでしょうか？
also... it inhibits the growth of bacteria
また...細菌の増殖を抑制します
that would also use some so-called intellectual healing
いわゆる知的療法も使用されるでしょう
For example, steroid suppression...
例えばステロイド抑制とか…
Steroids suppress immunity
ステロイドは免疫力を抑制する
then will...
そうすれば...
But what about the steroids?
しかし、ステロイドについてはどうでしょうか？
It enhances the growth of bacteria
細菌の増殖を促進します
So when the two drugs alternate
したがって、2つの薬が交互に使用されると、
It is currently a treatment for sepsis...
現在敗血症の治療中です...
a very important step
非常に重要なステップ
I will introduce our protagonist today
今日は主人公を紹介します
The main character is called...
主人公の名前は…
There was just a talk called Ibsidium 1
ちょうどイブシジウム 1 という話がありました
What about this anti-electric titanium?
この抗電チタンはどうでしょうか？
I got it from Spotted Grouper back then
あの頃マハタからもらった
Everyone must not know how to call it a little grouper
コハタの呼び方を誰もが知らないはず
It's all grouper anyway.
とにかく全部ハタです。
Because hairtail is now divided into
タコが分かれるようになったので、
Grouper is now divided into dragon belly grouper
ハタは現在、ドラゴンベリーハタに分類されています
What about dragon and tiger spots?
龍虎の斑点はどうでしょうか？
I actually can't figure it out myself
実は自分でも分かりません
Got a lot of different groupers
さまざまなハタがたくさんいます
Anyway, the tastiest one is the dragon and tiger stripes.
とにかく美味しいのは龍虎縞です。
This should be
これはそうあるべきです
Then in the process of eating fish
それから魚を食べる過程で
Everyone will think of something
誰もが何かを考えるだろう
You've killed fish, haven't you?
魚を殺してしまったのですね？
there may be some people who haven't killed fish
魚を殺したことがない人もいるかもしれない
That fish will be slippery, right?
その魚は滑りやすいでしょう？
you know fish can be slippery
魚は滑りやすいことを知っていますか
Then you know that in that year's luck
そうすれば、その年の運勢がわかるでしょう
Is there antistatic titanium?
帯電防止チタンはありますか？
may not know
知らないかもしれない
I told you in the grouper
ハタで言いました
Some Lucky Years contain anti-electric titanium
一部の幸運な年には、抗電気チタンが含まれています
very interesting
とても興味深い
why are you so funny
なぜあなたはそんなに面白いのですか
You think about our life I am in this air
あなたは私たちの人生について考えています、私はこの空気の中にいます
The one in Beijing is PM2.5, right?
北京のはPM2.5ですよね？
There is no news recently
最近ニュースがない
There is so-called anti-glory news in Beijing's shopping
北京のショッピング界にはいわゆる反栄光のニュースがある
Bury it there?
そこに埋めますか？
then think about it
それからそれについて考えてください
When we were kids we were fishing
私たちが子供の頃、私たちは釣りをしていました
when catching fish
魚を釣るとき
People say that if the water is clear, there will be no fish
水が澄んでいれば魚はいないと言われます
The water needs to be nourished by Pia
水にはピアが栄養を与える必要がある
There are many things in naked
裸でも色々あるよ
a lot of sand
たくさんの砂
a lot of bacteria
たくさんの細菌
so the water is naked
だから水は裸だ
when naked
裸のとき
Think about why you can grow up in such a naked environment
なぜそのような裸の環境で育つことができるのか考えてください
How good it is to grow fat and fat
どんどん太っていくのはなんて素晴らしいことだろう
That means its body is in the process of evolution
それはその体が進化の過程にあることを意味します
Is there a special mechanism evolved?
何か特別な仕組みが進化しているのでしょうか？
What is the mechanism of sterilization?
殺菌のメカニズムは何ですか？
ok
Ok
So I'm here to report
それで報告に来ました
The stone pound fish has an antibacterial
ストーンパウンドフィッシュには抗菌作用がある
It's called IPSYN1
それはIPSYN1と呼ばれます
Then this probably
それから、これはおそらく
We are currently in the laboratory
私たちは今研究室にいます
what we do antibacterial
私たちが行っていること 抗菌
It's about 21 MG acid
それは約21MGの酸です
Then it is the so-called sheep nose with double skin
それはいわゆるダブルスキンの羊鼻です
It is the difference between the so-called clear water and crisp water
いわゆる清水と清水の違いです
an ecology
一個生態
Then we are at IPSYN1
それから私たちはIPSYN1にいます
in our laboratory
私たちの研究室では
We have fought against swelling in the sentinel cabin
私たちは見張り小屋の腫れと闘ってきました
Some netizens watched biological disease resistance
一部のネチズンは生物学的耐病性を観察しました
I'm still immune and we're done.
私にはまだ免疫があるので、もう終わりです。
Then this is just a cute stone pound fish
それならこれはただのかわいい石ポンドの魚です
There are also a lot of stone pound fish industries in Taichung
台中には石ポンド漁業もたくさんあります
The other one is turtle fish, I want to report to you today
もう一つはカメウオです、今日はご報告したいと思います
This is the Pasidium IV of the turtle fish
こちらはカメウオのパシジウムⅣです
Then it comes from the so-called butter and turtle fish
それはいわゆるバターとタートルフィッシュから来ています
Then we synthesize 25 amino acids in the laboratory
次に、実験室で25個のアミノ酸を合成します。
What about the 25 amino acids, we have already done it in the laboratory
25 個のアミノ酸についてはどうでしょうか。実験室ではすでに実験済みです。
It is already known that it has antibacterial and anti-swelling effects
抗菌効果やむくみを抑える効果があることがわかっています。
I will report to you next time
次回ご報告させていただきます
The antibacterial ecology of Epsidium IV How do we do its biological activity
イプシジウム IV の抗菌生態学 その生物活性はどのように行われるのか
An interesting one, here I probably consist of these few
興味深いものです。ここではおそらくこれらのいくつかで構成されています
Report the results of several experiments
いくつかの実験の結果を報告する
One is the infection of Helicobacter pylori infection, and the other is the infection of MSA
1つはヘリコバクター・ピロリ感染、もう1つはMSAの感染です。
Then let's look at the infection of Helicobacter pylori infection first
それでは、まずヘリコバクター・ピロリ感染の感染状況を見てみましょう。
Everyone must, more or less I think
誰もが多かれ少なかれそうする必要があると思います
About 70% to 80% of the population in mainland China has Helicobacter pylori infection
中国本土では人口の約70％から80％がヘリコバクター・ピロリ菌に感染している
In Taiwan, I believe that there should be more than 40 to 50% of people who have had it
台湾では40～50％以上の人が罹患しているはずです。
Have had an infection without Helicobacter pylori infection in a lifetime
これまでにヘリコバクター・ピロリ菌に感染したことがない感染症歴がある
Then this is a beautiful bacterium again, every time I see this bacterium I get excited
それからまた綺麗な菌ですね、この菌を見るたびに興奮してしまいます
do you think it looks beautiful
綺麗だと思いますか？
beautiful isn't it
美しいですね
This bacterium has a lot of braided hairs that look like aliens
この細菌にはエイリアンのように見える編み毛がたくさんあります
can grasp the gastric mucosa
胃粘膜を把握できる
For a kid, a high school student should feel bad after seeing this
高校生がこれを見たら気分が悪くなるはず
But after you watch Alien
でも『エイリアン』を観た後は
I remember the first time in my life I watched a movie about a bunch of aliens called Liquid Ladder
人生で初めて『リキッド・ラダー』というエイリアンの集団についての映画を観たときのことを覚えています
I don't know if you've ever seen a liquid ladder
液体はしごを見たことがあるかどうかはわかりませんが、
have a thumb sticking out
親指が出ている
you know like its a thumb
あなたはそれが親指のようにわかるでしょう
Okay, gastric Helicobacter pylori
さて、胃のヘリコバクター・ピロリ菌
It is indeed a negative bacteria
まさに陰性菌です
a bacterium of its tiny oxygen
微量の酸素を持った細菌
The troublesome problem is gastric Helicobacter pylori
厄介なのは胃のピロリ菌
if you don't narrow it down
絞らないと
It may cause ulcers and stomach cancer in the future
将来潰瘍や胃がんの原因になる可能性がある
That's probably more than 80% of the generation
おそらく8割以上の世代がそうだろう
will not reveal any patients
患者を明らかにしない
that you will not hurt
あなたが傷つかないように
I won't feel my heart
心が感じられなくなるよ
I won't feel like hitting anything
何も叩く気がしない
neither will be fun
どちらも面白くないだろう
Then it has about 4 to 6 braids
三つ編みが4～6本くらいあります
who discovered Helicobacter eubacterium
ヘリコバクター・ユーバクテリウムを発見した人
Get someone if you can talk
話せるなら誰か誘ってよ
it was obtained by two scientists
それは二人の科学者によって得られたものです
This one is very simple to tell you
これを伝えるのはとても簡単です
just if you got
ちょうどあなたが得た場合
Because of our Helicobacter infection
ヘリコバクター感染のせいで
what will happen
何が起こるか
One is to sell into Wei Yan
一つは魏延に売り込むこと
The other one is to sell the shrunken Wei Yan
もう一つは、縮んだ魏延を売ることです。
Then his writing has been deformed.
その後、彼の文章は変形されました。
Another duodenal ulcer
また十二指腸潰瘍
In the end, the most troublesome thing is cancer
結局一番厄介なのはガンだよ
Cancer is really troublesome
癌って本当に厄介ですね
So what is currently the only cure for graceful idol infection?
それでは、現在、優雅なアイドル感染症に対する唯一の治療法は何でしょうか?
called antibiotics
抗生物質と呼ばれる
Everyone went to the hospital to finish the Wei Jing
みんなは魏京を終えるために病院へ行きました
The doctor said
医者は言いました
Excuse me
すみません
sir, miss
先生、お嬢さん
you got a graceful infection
あなたは優雅な感染症にかかりました
The doctor will prescribe medicine for you
医師はあなたのために薬を処方します
prescribe antibiotics
抗生物質を処方する
only antibiotics
抗生物質のみ
What other treatment? No
他にどのような治療法がありますか? いいえ
You just said you could have an important medical treatment?
重要な治療が受けられると言いましたね？
he said no
彼はノーと言った
You just need to eat once
一度食べればいいだけです
Very cheap
とても安い
need really cheap now
必要なものは今本当に安いです
because I did it myself twice
自分で2回やったから
Treatment of Weiyan striae infection
威延線条感染症の治療
my friend also found
私の友人も見つけました
They actually put a lot of different antibiotics
実際にはさまざまな抗生物質が投与されています
to do different treatments
さまざまな治療を行うために
now this is in
今これは入っています
A very similar one was published in 2011
2011年に発行された非常によく似たもの
Some of the currently used medical
現在使用されている医療品の一部
The three-in-one model of antibiotic treatment
抗生物質治療の 3 イン 1 モデル
But I'm breaking out with you that one of the antibiotics
でも、あなたに打ち明けたいのは、ある抗生物質のことです
This antibiotic is interesting
この抗生物質は面白いです
belly is nauseous bad fire
お腹が吐き気がしてひどい火事です
stomach ache
腹痛
Bump
凹凸
have vomiting and diarrhea
嘔吐と下痢がある
It then affects some liver functions
その後、一部の肝機能に影響を及ぼします
or disabled patients
または障害のある患者さん
Causes excessive moisture growth of non-susceptible molds
過剰な湿気により、感受性の低いカビが発生する
Then because of the superior blind spiral sense
そして優れたブラインドスパイラルセンスのおかげで
Because drug resistance develops in a small number of patients
少数の患者に薬剤耐性が発生するため
still develop resistance
まだ耐性ができている
Everyone remember to go back first
みんな最初に戻ることを忘れないでね
If you think of what you are studying in Xinjiang today
今、新疆で何を学んでいるのかを考えてみると、
must remember drug resistance
薬剤耐性を覚えておく必要があります
bacterial resistance
細菌耐性
it's a very important noun
それはとても重要な名詞です
Another one is to say
もう一つはこう言うことです
a lot of these drugs
これらの薬の多く
If it is taken with other actually anti-drugs
他の実際の抗薬と併用した場合
Troublesome things that can cause some systemic metabolism
全身代謝を引き起こす可能性のある厄介なこと
So it is in patients allergic to these anti-drugs
したがって、これらの抗薬に対してアレルギーのある患者にはそれが起こります
it is unusable
使えない
But I remember the doctor didn't seem to ask me so much
でも医者はあまり質問しなかったようだったのを覚えています
He just prescribed the medicine
彼はちょうど薬を処方したところだ
So we pass
それで合格します
We will report to you first
まずはご報告させていただきます
The antidote for vomiting and diarrhea just now
今の嘔吐と下痢の解毒剤
We use electronic small cloud mirror
電子小型雲鏡を使用しております
Just now there is a video to report to all of you
只今、皆様にご報告する動画がございます
That is to say it will really
つまり本当にそうなります
Impressed by our Luo Sheng bacteria
当社の羅生菌に感動
Slowly it will bubble after touching
触れるとゆっくり泡立ちます
The contents will flow out
中身が流れ出てしまう
so you can see it's targeting
ターゲットを絞っていることがわかります
resembling a micro throw shape
マイクロスローの形状に似ています
To do the mechanism of impressing
感動させる仕組みを行うには
this is a cartoon
これは漫画です
TP4 it produces a pattern
TP4 パターンを生成します
It is similar to a carpet pattern
絨毯のような模様です
covered in bacteria
細菌にまみれた
needs to be used on the cell membrane
細胞膜に使用する必要がある
then it goes inside
それから中に入ります
resembling a microprojectile
微小発射体に似ている
go in and impress it later
後で行って感動してください
let the contents flow out
中身を流れ出させて
And cause the death of Youneng Helix
そしてユネン・ヘリックスを死に至らしめる
At the same time, on the antigenic state of the grouper
同時にハタの抗原状態について
We also did a similar experiment
私たちも同様の実験をしました
You can see that in this
これを見ればわかります
Electronic villain inspection map
電子小人驗圖
You can see it's all broken too
全部壊れているのもわかります
these bacteria are interesting
この細菌は面白いですね
processed by these antigenic states
これらの抗原状態によって処理される
Bacteria completely disintegrated
バクテリアは完全に分解されました
Do you think of an interesting story
面白い話を思いつきますか
These bacteria disintegrate
これらの細菌は分解します
what will it become
それは何になりますか
If you have learned
学んだことがあれば
If you have a little impression
少しでも感想があれば
that is you will
あなたがそうするのですか
Do Chinese medicine practitioners say what to eat to make up for you?
漢方医は、食べたもので補えると言うのでしょうか？
right
右
you know these broken things
あなたはこれらの壊れたものを知っています
actually a good
実際に良い
That is to say, it can cause the body's immune response to become an antibody
つまり、体の免疫反応が抗体になる可能性があります。
But antibodies can be synthesized in the future
しかし将来的には抗体が合成される可能性がある
Re-cleaning a new antigen
新しい抗原の再洗浄
So in the process of making a vaccine in the antigenic state
したがって、抗原性の状態でワクチンを製造する過程で
Emerging in the process of making a vaccine
ワクチン製造の過程で登場
We use this model
私たちはこのモデルを使用しています
Go do some research on deep water life
深海生物について調べに行きましょう
And got a pretty good research result
そしてかなり良い研究結果が出ました
Then you can see that EPI is in
EPI が入っていることがわかります。
Its mode is not the same as the mode since TP4 Wuguo just now
そのモードは先ほどのTP4 Wuguo以降のモードと同じではありません
You can see that it's a
であることがわかります。
A bubble is a shape of a saddle created like this
バブルとはこうやって作ったサドルの形です
Then it popped like a balloon
それからそれは風船のように弾けました
Then break the cell coin or cell bone of this bacteria
次に、この細菌の細胞コインまたは細胞骨を破壊します。
then it broke
それから壊れた
Of course everyone just saw the so-called
もちろん、誰もがいわゆるものを見ただけです
Experiments in the chamber
チャンバー内での実験
It's what we call an intraventricular experiment.
それはいわゆる脳室内実験です。
Invisal's experiment
インヴィサルの実験
Everyone will ask me
誰もが私に尋ねます
Mr. Chen, you are really good at bragging
チェンさんは本当に自慢が上手です
So what's going on inside the animal body?
では、動物の体内では何が起こっているのでしょうか？
So let's try feeding the mice
それでは、ネズミに餌をあげてみましょう
because everyone likes me mouse
みんなが私のことが好きだからマウス
Why
なぜ
Rats are all rats from heaven
ネズミはみんな天国から来たネズミだ
So when you grow up, you have to do mouse experiments
だから大人になったらマウス実験をしなければならない
let's see then
それでは見てみましょう
We just started buying a bunch of rats that came in
私たちは入ってきたネズミを大量に買い始めたところです
Of course these rats are not what everyone imagines outside
もちろん、これらのネズミは誰もが外で想像しているものではありません
caught those mice
あのネズミを捕まえた
I remember when we were kids we were near the sugar cane fields
私たちが子供の頃、サトウキビ畑の近くにいたことを覚えています
Sugarcane field full of voles
ハタネズミがいっぱいのサトウキビ畑
When you grab it, it's narrow enough to make soup with vegetables
握ると狭いので野菜スープも作れます
But these mice are not this kind of mice
しかし、これらのマウスはこの種のマウスではありません
It's an SPF mouse, a very expensive one.
SPFマウスです、とても高価なものです。
This one of its white mice is white and fat
この白いネズミは白くて太っています
Challenges that allow you to do different bacteria
さまざまな細菌を実験できるようにするチャレンジ
then let you know say
そしてあなたに知らせてこう言います
Did this experimental rat succeed?
この実験用ネズミは成功したのでしょうか？
Of course animal rights groups may seriously protest that
もちろん、動物愛護団体はこれに真剣に抗議するかもしれない
This white mouse can actually be a stupid mouse
この白いネズミは実は愚かなネズミである可能性があります
But these white mice
でもこの白いネズミは
On the development of our biomedicine
私たちの生物医学の開発について
They really are our heroes
彼らは本当に私たちのヒーローです
unsung post-pregnancy animal heroes
妊娠後の知られざる動物ヒーローたち
What are we doing with these unsung animal heroes now
知られざる動物のヒーローたちと今私たちは何をしているのか
Just let it acclimate to the environment for a while
しばらく環境に慣らしてください
Then do two infections
次に 2 つの感染を実行します
Just let it have in the stomach
お腹の中に入れておくだけ
Because of the growth of pylorospira infection
ピロスピラ感染症の増殖のため
After growing we can put the mouse
成長したらマウスを入れることができます
After a week of growth
一週間の成長を経て
In time, we slaughtered the mice in the mouse part
やがて、ネズミ部分のネズミを屠殺しました。
then feed it inside
それから中に餌を与えます
Take a look to see if there is any generation of Yumen Luoxuan in it
玉門羅軒の世代が含まれているかどうかを確認してください。
because if not
そうでなければ
We mean we can't drug it
つまり、麻薬は使えないということです
Then we took what you all saw just now
それから私たちは皆さんが今見たものを撮りました
Shipan Fish Soup is the soup above the turtle
Shipan Fish Soupは亀の上のスープです
The Anti-Yantai We Got
私たちが得た反煙台
like you eat cold syrup
冷たいシロップを食べるように
Didi
ディディ
it didn't drip
滴りませんでした
I don't know what rats taste like
ネズミの味がわからない
Then I think it's Didi
それならディディだと思います
Didi poured it into the rat's feed
ディディはそれをネズミの餌に注ぎました
let it eat
食べさせてください
So the rats ate for 14 days
それで、ネズミは14日間食べました
We'll kill the rats again in two weeks
2週間後にまたネズミを殺します
then watch it feed inside
それからそれが中で餌をやるのを見てください
Is there any production of Youmen Luoxuan?
楊門羅軒の演出はあるのでしょうか？
We did a total of three different experiments
合計 3 つの異なる実験を行いました
An anti-yantai called rockfish
メバルと呼ばれるアンチヤンタイ
An anti-yantai called turtle fish
亀の魚と呼ばれる反煙台
One is currently used clinically
そのうちの1つは現在臨床で使用されています
Three-in-one Anti-Agarin
スリーインワン抗アガリン
But we didn't make one here
しかし、私たちはここでそれを作りませんでした
Experiments with self-acids
自己酸の実験
because we thought of saying
私たちが言おうと思ったから
Will there be no need to use self-acid in the future?
将来的にはセルフアシッドを使用する必要はなくなるのでしょうか？
you can pour the medicine in
薬を注ぐことができます
So the experiment we poured in
そこで私たちが注ぎ込んだ実験は
You can see this red mark error
この赤いマークのエラーが表示されます
on the turtle fish
カメの魚について
Anti-smoke titanium obtained above
上記で得られた防煙チタン
You can see after we kill the rats
ネズミを殺したらわかるよ
Where are these mice?
これらのネズミはどこにいますか?
6 mice we got
ゲットしたマウスは6匹
It turns out there's really nothing in it
実は何も入っていないことが判明
Production of gastric pyloric helix infection
胃幽門ヘリックス感染症の発症
We get really low levels of fine smoke from the stomach
胃から出る微細な煙は非常に低レベルです
But without any medication
でも薬も何も使わずに
its fine smoke is really high
その細かい煙は本当に高いです
You can see this 6
これを見ればわかります6
Digital Moon High Represents
デジタルムーンハイ代表
Rats with higher levels of fine smoke
細かい煙のレベルが高いラット
Digital month low represents
デジタル月の最低値を表す
The amount of fine smoke in the mouse body is less
マウス本体内の細かい煙の量が少ない
But you can see the three-in-one drug
しかし、スリーインワン薬はわかります
You can see its gastric pyloric helix infection
胃幽門ヘリックス感染が見られます
still very high
まだ非常に高い
Probably between 4, 4 and 5
おそらく4、4、5の間です
but we can see here
しかし、ここで見ることができます
Probably below 1
おそらく1以下
The benefits of eating more black mushroom fish
黒キノコ魚をもっと食べることの利点
Then this black mushroom fish is in the ecology we synthesized
そして、この黒いキノコ魚は私たちが合成した生態系の中にあります
you can see we are
私たちがいるのがわかります
This little bit of red is like thin smoke
このほんの少しの赤は 薄い煙のようだ
You can see that we use
を使用していることがわかります
a particular coloring pattern
特定のカラーリングパターン
can see it these
これらは見えます
what about these
これらはどうですか
This time with a three-in-one
今回はスリーインワンで
Mice treated with anti-smoke
抗煙剤で治療されたマウス
It still produces fine smoke
相変わらず細かい煙が出ます
But we use the anti-smoke of black mushroom fish to get in too much
でも入りすぎると黒キノコ魚の防煙剤を使うんだよ
Because there is basically no bacteria produced when it is ground inside.
なぜなら、内部で粉砕する際には基本的に細菌が発生しないからです。
Those people didn't use any treatment first.
それらの人々は最初はいかなる治療も受けませんでした。
It turns out that it has a lot of bacteria producing
細菌が大量に発生していることが分かりました
You see that click-throughs represent bacteria
Click-to-Read が細菌を表していることがわかります。
Those are bacteria
あれは細菌です
What about these groupers
これらのハタはどうですか
An antigen embryo obtained by clicking on a grouper
ハタをクリックして得られる抗原胚
You can also see the same result
同じ結果を確認することもできます
This red is also marked
この赤もマークされています
That is to say, the antigen embryo obtained from the grouper
つまり、ハタから得られた抗原胚
It is also possible to put rats in the stomach
ネズミを胃の中に入れることも可能
The stomach feeling is very low
胃の調子が非常に悪い
So this gives us a new hope
これは私たちに新たな希望を与えてくれます
I just had a Psychedelic
サイケデリックを飲んだばかりだ
Tell everyone about the emerging drugs in the future of mankind
人類の未来に登場する新薬についてみんなに伝えましょう
Could it be obtained from water porridge?
水粥から摂取できるのでしょうか？
That's the very special PCR principle we use
これが私たちが使用する非常に特殊な PCR 原理です
There is also the Western target point analysis method of the protein pattern
タンパク質パターンの西洋ターゲットポイント解析法もあります
Verify that there is still a mouse in the body
体内にマウスがまだ存在することを確認します
yes and those bacteria
はい、そしてそれらの細菌
Then we can all find out that
そうすれば私たち全員がそれを知ることができます
If there is no treatment, there are antigens to eat
治療法がない場合、抗原を食べる必要がある
Basically you can see that there are no class fragments here
基本的に、ここにはクラスフラグメントがないことがわかります。
without any white fragments
白い破片が無い状態で
It means that there is no such bacteria produced
そういう菌はいないということです
Ok so we get an interesting result
さて、興味深い結果が得られました
that is
あれは
This mouse is very cute. The mouse ate Youmenyou's sour bacteria
このネズミはとてもかわいいです。ネズミはヨウメンヨウの酸っぱい菌を食べました
It really has Acidophilus bacteria in it
実はアシドフィルス菌が入っているんです
very similar to human infection
人への感染と非常によく似ている
Humans are also passed through food, kissing, and infection
人間は食事、キス、感染症によっても感染します。
We also let it eat our disease-resistant fetus later
後で病気に強い胎児も食べさせます
Through these experiments, we all found that it really chewed off
これらの実験を通じて、私たちは皆、それが本当に噛み砕いていることを発見しました
This is our conclusion that
これが私たちの結論です。
I have not mentioned some regulatory factors of immunity here
ここでは免疫の制御因子については言及しませんでした
because that is cumbersome
それは面倒だから
So I can only talk about the results of animal experiments
だから私は動物実験の結果についてしか話せません
Then what is my second little experiment to report to you?
それでは、私があなたに報告する 2 番目の小さな実験は何ですか?
Everyone will be tired, right?
みんな疲れますよね？
there may be some people who are not tired
疲れない人もいるかもしれない
But when I was in college I was tired and miserable
でも大学時代は疲れていて惨めだった
Tired and painful Tired and miserable
疲れて苦しい 疲れて惨めだ
just fell off a motorcycle
バイクから落ちたばかり
You can see that car slowly coming
あの車がゆっくりと近づいてくるのが見える
People slowly rubbed against the ground
人々はゆっくりと地面をこすった
Then you wonder why my parking space can't be blocked
では、なぜ私の駐車スペースが塞がれないのか不思議に思うでしょう
Why does it keep coming to the opposite parking space?
なぜ向かいの駐車場に何度も来るのでしょうか？
And when you get up you see a little gash on your leg
そして立ち上がると、足に小さな傷があるのが見えます
You touch that gun and it won't hurt
その銃に触れても痛くないよ
Really I think the wheel is really very very
本当に、ホイールは本当にとてもとても良いと思います
You won't find out until you wake up and find it broken
目覚めて壊れていることに気づくまでは分からないだろう
Why is your leg hurting and bleeding
足が痛くて出血しているのはなぜですか
Alright, everyone, did you think you would stay
さて、皆さん、残ると思いましたか？
Have you looked closely at your wounds?
自分の傷をよく観察しましたか？
The wound will flow out in the process of bathing in the river
川で水浴びをしているうちに傷が流れ出てしまう
yellow sticky sticky
黄色の粘着性粘着性
Sometimes it smells so bad
時々すごく臭いがすることがあります
right
右
Have you ever touched and smelled it yourself?
自分で触ったり、匂いを嗅いだりしたことはありますか？
you know what that is
それが何なのか知っていますか
that very very very interesting person
とてもとてもとても興味深い人
I may really have nothing to do since I was in college.
大学時代から本当に何もすることがなかったのかもしれない。
internal trouble
内部トラブル
it's itchy
かゆいです
Itches and you want to pull out the wound
かゆくて傷口を抜きたくなる
In the process of pulling it up, it will start to bathe in the wound
引き上げる途中で傷口に浸み始める
I just look at my wounds every day
毎日自分の傷ばかり見てる
start to bathe in the river
開始浴河
Then there is a little white yellow juice flowing out
すると少し白黄色の濃厚な汁が流れ出てきます
And then it smells really good
そして、とてもいい匂いがするんです
I later found out that it was bacteria
後から細菌だったことが分かりました
immune cells in your body
あなたの体の免疫細胞
Giant Cell Moderate HP
巨大細胞中程度のHP
The structure under the suspicion of contact with bacteria
細菌との接触が疑われる構造
stinks is some of it
臭いのは一部です
that product
その製品
Alright, let's talk to you now
さて、今から話しましょう
Everyone must remember
誰もが覚えているはずです
These two things happened in 2014 and 2015
これら 2 つの出来事は 2014 年と 2015 年に起こりました
How many people died, how many people were injured
何人が死亡し、何人が負傷したのか
We won't be a rich prize here
ここでは高額な賞品にはなりません
but it's a hassle
でも面倒だ
so traumatized
とてもトラウマになった
Everyone should see
みんなも見るべきだよ
Mr. Chen, you always ride a motorcycle
チェンさんはいつもバイクに乗っていますね
a wound like a big one
大きな傷のようなトラウマ
You're still here to tell us all
あなたはまだ私たちにすべてを伝えるためにここにいます
Tell us about science salary
科学者の給与について教えてください
Then why do these people just hang up?
では、なぜこの人たちはすぐに電話を切るのでしょうか？
wait a minute and you'll see
ちょっと待ってください、そうすればわかります
little trauma
ちょっとしたトラウマ
mainly cause them
主にそれらを引き起こす
they get bacterial infections
彼らは細菌感染症にかかります
At the same time, I also got what I just reported to you
同時に、先ほど報告した内容も得ました
sepsis after bacterial infection
細菌感染後の敗血症
So we experimentally
そこで私たちは実験的に
we just want us to hurt
私たちはただ傷つきたいだけなの
Because I just reported to you
さっき報告したばかりなので
Although I studied marine biology in college
大学では海洋生物学を勉強していましたが、
But when I was in college, I used to take pictures of horse races
でも学生時代はよく競馬の写真を撮っていました
Then the photos of the horse race often leave the disabled
そして、競馬の写真はしばしば障害者を残す
Trauma
トラウマ
so i just keep watching my legs
だから私はただ自分の足を見続けるだけ
I can think about it later
後から考えてもいいよ
One day in the middle of the lab I found out that the mouse is a great friend again
ある日、研究室の途中で、ネズミがまた素晴らしい友達であることに気づきました。
another unsung hero
もう一人の知られざる英雄
Well the unsung hero we bought these mice again
さて、縁の下の力持ち、私たちはこれらのマウスを再び購入しました
Then we created a 1 cm by 1 cm wound on him
それから私たちは彼に1cm×1cmの傷を作りました
So what do we deal with this trauma? Deal with the antibacterial state
では、このトラウマにどう対処すればいいのでしょうか? 抗菌状態に対処するのです。
This is what we use Staphylococcus aureus
これは黄色ブドウ球菌に使用されるものです
Oxygen Resistant
耐酸素性
Staphylococcus aureus
黄色ブドウ球菌
This bacterial infection is currently in the hospital
この細菌感染症で現在入院中です
Still a bacterial infection with a really bad headache
まだ細菌感染症があり、ひどい頭痛が続いています
is a lot of time
時間はたくさんあります
Then let's take this mouse
それならこのマウスを持って行きましょう
Doesn't it have iron plates with a size of 1 cm and 1 cm square on its back?
背中に1cmと1cm角の鉄板が貼ってあったじゃないですか。
The mouse will come out with a slight trauma
ネズミは軽い外傷を負って出てきます
Then we take the amount of bacteria to the 6th power of 10
次に、細菌の量を 10 の 6 乗します。
10 to the power of 6 the amount of bacteria each mouse drops on it
10 の 6 乗、各マウスがその上に落とす細菌の量
This bacteria will grow on the back of its mouse
この細菌はマウスの背中で増殖します
then becomes an infected open wound
その後、感染した開いた傷になります
As you can see this has been the result of what I think we did for 14 days
ご覧のとおり、これは私たちが 14 日間行ったことの結果です。
Report to everyone that this is the plugging group
これがプラグイングループであることを全員に報告します
It's the control group, it's the mouse
それはコントロールグループ、それはマウスです
Did not put any bacteria, and did not put any treatment
菌も入れず、トリートメントも一切入れていません
it will add up by itself, it will start
それは自動的に加算されます、それは始まります
Because it uses its own body immunity to do wound healing
自身の体の免疫を使って傷を治癒するため
But there is MRSA, have you seen the yellow over here
でもMRSAがいます、ここの黄色を見たことありますか？
we're the ones who stink and have fun
臭くて楽しんでるのは私たちだ
This is the result of bacterial infection
これは細菌感染によるものです
It's about ninety-six hours after the fourth day
4日目から約96時間後
The mouse is dead
ネズミが死んだ
But if because it's MRSA bacteria
でもMRSA菌だからなら
It allows the so-called venomission
それはいわゆる毒を与えることを可能にします
All things, enzymes, antibiotics for treatment
治療のためのあらゆるもの、酵素、抗生物質
because it's going to kill this, i just said
それはこれを殺すことになるから、私はただ言った
There are some antibiotics that kill certain bacteria
特定の細菌を殺す抗生物質がいくつかあります
Some bacteria can be killed by certain antibiotics
一部の細菌は特定の抗生物質で殺すことができます
You can see that the skin is still very well restored
肌がまだ非常に回復しているのがわかります
very beautiful
非常に美しい
But if this MRSA bacteria
しかし、もしこのMRSA菌が
Because the M is the antibiotic
Mは抗生物質だから
This MRSA bacteria, because resistant to this antibiotic
このMRSA菌は、この抗生物質に耐性があるため、
So even if you go on this antibiotic
したがって、この抗生物質を飲み続けたとしても
The mouse is over
マウスは終わりました
Simple and easy to report to everyone
シンプルでみんなに報告しやすい
Maybe watch me here for a second
ちょっとここで私を見てください
This mouse is dead
このネズミは死んだ
but think about it
でも考えてみてください
on top of humans
人間の上に
If you experience a bacterial infection with this antibiotic
この抗生物質で細菌感染症を起こした場合
It will hang up in 96 hours soon
もうすぐ96時間後に切れます
so you think about it
だからあなたはそれについて考えます
We are looking for a new
新しい方を探しています
Drugs that can replace antibiotics
抗生物質の代わりとなる薬
ok let's see next
はい、次を見ましょう
EPI is what I just told you
EPI は今お話ししたとおりです
Antibacterial status obtained by pointing on the rice
お米を指差して抗菌ステータスを取得
The probability of 33 is that I just reported to you
確率 33 は、先ほど報告したとおりです
That one nose got antibacterial status
片方の鼻が抗菌ステータスになった
Add collagen this time
今度はコラーゲンを加えます
Because everyone is emphasizing beauty now
今はみんな美しさを重視しているから
When many wounds heal
たくさんの傷が癒えるとき
no scars
傷跡はありません
or if you are on medication
または薬を服用している場合
I also want collagen
コラーゲンも欲しい
Can promote wound healing
創傷治癒を促進することができる
we can see that is to say
つまり、
Meals also come to an antibacterial state
食事も抗菌状態に
how well its wounds heal
その傷はどのくらい治るのか
very beautiful by the tenth day
10日目にはとても綺麗になりました
All the hair has grown back
髪の毛も全部生えてきました
if you add collagen
コラーゲンを加えると
Its fur grows more beautifully and faster
毛皮はより美しく、より速く成長します
So we believe in collagen
だから私たちはコラーゲンを信じています
We see him mixed in with the anti-morbid process
私たちは彼が抗病的プロセスに混ざっているのを見ます
Just now as a raw drug
今まさに生薬として
Quality of Raw Drugs
原薬の品質
Then he went forward and came out
それから彼は前に出て出てきました
so he can see him
そうすれば彼は彼を見ることができる
When the third day started here
3日目はこちら
and a little yellow
そして少し黄色
But in the end he did really well
でも最後には彼は本当によくやってくれた
Let's look at the angiogenesis treated by these drugs
これらの薬剤によって治療される血管新生を見てみましょう
Why do you want to explode angiogenesis with everyone?
なぜみんなで血管新生を爆発させたいのですか？
you may not know
あなたは知らないかもしれません
there are some models
いくつかのモデルがあります
or some ambiguous people
または曖昧な人
It's not just a trio of jades
それはただの翡翠のトリオではありません
Some people because he wants to wear
彼が着たいからという人もいる
wear some swimwear
水着を着てください
or some people
または何人かの人々
he has three mouths in the face
彼の顔には口が3つある
He hoped that his three jades would be on Mino Medicine
三つの口がミノ薬になることを望んでいる
I hope he will have a lot of angiogenesis
彼に血管新生がたくさん起こることを願っています
Because this will cause a scar to come out
傷跡が残る原因になるので
so you can see
それでわかります
We are in the whole process of angiogenesis
私たちは血管新生の全過程にいます
If you have added anti-morbid process
防病加工を加えた場合
You can all see it like this anti-morbid
あなたは皆、この反病的なもののように見ることができます
or this flounder's disease-resistant
またはこのヒラメの病気に強い
You can see that his angiogenesis is beautiful
血管新生が美しいことがわかります
If comparing a control group
対照群を比較する場合
Or for groups with ice or microphones
または、氷やマイクを持ったグループ向け
he finally
彼はついに
Those new students are very beautiful
あの新入生はとても美しいです
then it has another
それから別のものがあります
The other is called can promote
もう 1 つは、プロモーションできると呼ばれる
Stimulus for production technology
生産技術への刺激
We are still doing related research
現在も関連研究を行っています
Then we can report to you
それでは、ご報告させていただきます
This is the main part of MRSA
これがMRSAの主要な部分です
I just told you
私はちょうどあなたに言いました
Is the ancestor dead?
先祖は亡くなったのか？
But scientific research cannot say that he is dead
しかし科学的研究では彼が死亡したとは言えません
Scientific research must ask why
科学研究はその理由を問う必要がある
Has the number of bacteria in the ancestors been suppressed?
祖先の細菌の数は抑制されていますか？
If it's not pressed down you can see it's funny
押されていなければおかしいのがわかります
Sometimes we go home when the drug is actually administered
実際に薬が投与されているときに家に帰ることもあります
medicine prescribed by your doctor
医師が処方した薬
Everyone take one medicine and you don't take it if you feel better
誰もが1つの薬を服用し、気分が良くなったら服用しないでください
Doctors sometimes prescribe a three- or seven-day regimen
医師は 3 日間または 7 日間の処方を処方することもあります
there is a reason for it
それには理由があります
For example, when your bacterial count is suppressed
たとえば、細菌数が抑制されている場合
you feel like a doctor
あなたは医者のような気分です
No more antibiotics or medicine
もう抗生物質も薬も要らない
Then your bacteria count went up again
その後、細菌数が再び増加しました
Then what will happen after this goes up?
では、これが上がった後はどうなるでしょうか？
secondary infection
二次感染
then it was more troublesome
そしたらもっと面倒だった
So you can see that is
つまり、それがわかります
We use Jialin Xilin as just mentioned
私たちは Jialin を使用します Xilin がちょうど言った
More troublesome, he has many side effects
さらに厄介なことに、彼には多くの副作用があります
but now
でも今
If this anti-pseudobacteria
抗偽性細菌であれば、
in mice
マウスの中で
It's about the fourth day it's all dead
全部死んで4日目くらいです
So the bacteria here just can't see any bacteria
つまり、ここのバクテリアにはバクテリアが見えないのです
We can't see the fungus that we drew blood from the mice
マウスから血液を採取した菌は見えません
But if you use the TP3 from the turtle and hedgehog
しかし、カメとハリネズミのTP3を使用すると、
Or the EBI from the grouper hedgehog
またはハタハリネズミのEBI
You can see it on day 17
17日目からご覧になれます
Its bacterial count is almost zero
細菌数はほぼゼロです
It means that it no longer has this kind of bacteria in its body
これは、体内にこの種の細菌が存在しなくなったことを意味します
These bacteria were killed by our anti-pregnancy
これらの細菌は私たちの抗妊娠剤によって死滅しました
So anti-pregnancy may be a
したがって、反妊娠は可能性があります
the future may be a
将来的には
Medicines for burns and skin infections
火傷および皮膚感染症の薬
Everyone will definitely say that Mr. Chen knew that he was a mouse
誰もが間違いなく、チェン氏は自分がネズミであることを知っていたと言うだろう。
How do I know the rats are fun for everyone
ネズミが誰にとっても楽しいものだとどうやってわかりますか
Every time you make a mouse, you will have a lot of
マウスを作るたびに、たくさんのものが手に入ります。
Experimental results that seem to have potential
可能性を秘めていると思われる実験結果
So we're going to be pigs
だから俺たちは豚になるんだ
Then why else?
では、なぜ他にあるのでしょうか？
Because of the pig I think I have a real bond with it
豚のおかげで私は豚と本当の絆を持っていると思う
If this pig succeeds
この豚が成功したら
It will also be similar to medium and large animals.
それは中型および大型の動物にも似ています。
Then what's the king next?
では、次は王様は何でしょうか？
We hope to be able to enter the so-called clinical testing
いわゆる臨床試験に参入できることを期待しています
For example, using monkeys or using pre-clinical tests to find some CRL companies
たとえば、サルを使用したり、前臨床試験を使用して CRL 企業を見つけたりします。
It is the clinical testing company that helps us do these tests
これらの検査を支援してくれるのは臨床検査会社です
You can see that it is the same in the experimental process of strains
菌株の実験過程でも同様であることがわかります
We use the anti-morbidity from the grouper
ハタ類の抗疾病効果を利用しています。
We use 1000 times or 100 times or 10 times the number of MIC
MIC の数の 1000 倍、100 倍、または 10 倍を使用します。
In addition, we have a 14-party MSA that is 10 higher on the plant this time.
さらに、今回のプラントには 10 高い 14 パーティの MSA があります。
you can see it to the end
最後まで見ることができます
In fact, the wound area is doing very well.
実際、傷部分の状態は非常に良好です。
10 of 14 party MSA, you can see its bacteria and its wound sealing speed is not so fast
14 パーティの MSA のうち 10 個。細菌が確認でき、傷をふさぐ速度はそれほど速くありません。
In all this 25th day
この25日目の間に
Look at the different bacterial infections and different treatment processes this time
今回は、さまざまな細菌感染症とさまざまな治療プロセスを見てみましょう。
For example, we use 10 times the number of MIC
たとえば、MIC の 10 倍の数を使用します。
MIC is the minimum concentration of bacteria that can kill bacteria
MICは細菌を殺すことができる細菌の最小濃度です
You can see the amount of EPI we use 10 times the MIC
MIC の 10 倍の EPI が使用されていることがわかります。
You can see it grow over time
時間の経過とともに成長するのがわかります
it precloses the wound very well
傷を非常によく事前にふさぎます
If you use 100 times the amount of MIC
MICを100倍使用した場合
It wound up running away for the last 25 days
結局25日間逃げ続けた
will run faster
より速く実行されます
Kamdor is like a mouse
カムドールはネズミのようだ
nothing goes out
何も出ない
just heat it up
ただ温めるだけ
If we use 1000 times the MIC
MIC の 1000 倍を使用すると
this EPI
このEPI
then you can see
そうすればわかります
it is also
それも
Also the wound is also very good
傷もとても綺麗です
but we later
しかし、私たちは後で
If it is really eaten at the waist
本当に腰で食べられたら
We don't need to use 1000 times
1000回も使う必要はない
that is expensive
それは高価です
so we can grab a
をつかむことができます
good connections
良い接続
market we are above pigs
マーケット、我々は豚の上にいる
good results on mice
マウスで良い結果が得られた
We also get good results on pigs
豚でも良い結果が得られています
make us more confident
私たちにもっと自信を与えてください
Can advance to clinical
臨床に進むことができる
So we can all report
みんなで報告できるように
Anti-Tiantai MAB can be used as
Anti-Tiantai MAB は次のように使用できます。
I also come to fight the substitute
私も代役と戦いに来ます
Then Anti-Tiantai did not cause immune stimulation
すると、反天台は免疫刺激を引き起こさなかった
At least we have partial results
少なくとも部分的な結果は得られています
have told us
私たちに言いました
It does not cause bothersome immune stimulation
煩わしい免疫刺激を引き起こしません
Another one is
もう一つは、
We hope that the research results can be sold into clinical trials.
研究結果が臨床試験に販売されることを願っています
Everyone after Lei gave birth
レイちゃん出産後の皆さん
A foreshadowing of what I just said
今言ったことの伏線
After Lei gave birth, I said
レイが出産した後、私はこう言いました。
You won't be in pain during Ray's process
レイのプロセス中に痛みを感じることはありません
But when it thunders you will hurt
でも雷が鳴ったら傷つくよ
Everyone will feel pain
誰もが痛みを感じるでしょう
in the burn process
燃焼過程で
or when you pick your wounds
または傷をほじるとき
Everyone will be in pain, it is impossible that no one will not be in pain, right?
誰もが痛みを感じるでしょう、痛みを感じない人がいないということはあり得ませんよね？
Well, in the process of going through the pain, you will think of one thing
さて、痛みを経験する過程で、あなたは一つのことを考えるでしょう
Is there any possibility of anti-morbidity in treating the wound healing process
創傷治癒過程の治療に抗罹患性の可能性はありますか
Make wounds painless, or humans painless, or animals painless
傷の痛みをなくす、人間の痛みをなくす、動物の痛みをなくす
So I went to find a very good friend named Teacher Wen Zhirong
そこで私は温志龍先生というとても仲の良い友達を探しに行きました。
He is a teacher at Zhongshan University
彼は中山大学の教師です
We use an anti-pathological agent called PCDI1
当院ではPCDI1と呼ばれる抗病理学的薬剤を使用しています。
In 2015 we were able to know that
2015年に私たちはそれを知ることができました
We know from the ancestors that it is anti-morbid
私たちは祖先からそれが抗病的であることを知っています
It actually has the effect of suppressing pain
実は痛みを抑える効果があるのです
it's really fun
本当に楽しいです
So we hope to develop into a drug in the future
ですので、将来的には医薬品としての開発も期待しています。
Applying this can not only make the wound heal well
これを塗ると傷の治りが良くなるだけでなく、
It can kill bacteria and make the pain less painful
細菌を殺し、痛みを軽減することができます
you may not know
あなたは知らないかもしれません
those in the process of burn injury
火傷の進行中の人
For example, the gas explosion in Kaohsiung just mentioned
例えば、先ほどの高雄のガス爆発。
or a burn at an amusement park
遊園地で火傷したり
General burns such as general chairs
一般椅子などの一般火傷
In fact, there are already flower feet at home.
実は、すでに家にも花が咲いています。
If the whole body has 2, 30% barbecue
全身2、30％焼きなら
that was excruciatingly painful
それは耐え難いほど痛かった
So our Western family is on drug development
つまり、私たちの西洋人家族は医薬品の開発に取り組んでいます
In addition to our drug can have many different functions
私たちの薬に加えて、さまざまな機能があります
I'm going to talk about my last chop
私の最後のチョップについて話します
The last study result
最後一個研究結果
I told you about cancer when I first started
最初に癌について話しました
3 million is not a small number
300万って決して小さい数字ではない
Ordinary people in the process of cancer treatment
がん治療中の一般の方
For example, the process of doing PL-1
たとえば、PL-1を行うプロセス
Now the latest process is 3 million
現在、最新のプロセスは 300 万です
But is there any possibility that we can reduce the process of it
しかし、そのプロセスを減らすことができる可能性はありますか?
lower its price
価格を下げる
Because we use a simple anti-pregnancy state for treatment
治療には単純な抗妊娠状態を使用するため
This is an anti-pregnancy state we got
これが私たちが得た妊娠禁止状態です
We do some antibacterial ecology
抗菌エコロジーを行っています
3491 articles were published from 1990 to 2015
1990 年から 2015 年までに 3491 件の記事が公開されました
currently existing
現在現有的
Our anti-pregnancy state, let us first introduce
私たちの反妊娠状態、まずはご紹介しましょう
This generation is an anti-pregnancy state above the flounder
この世代はヒラメ以上の反妊娠状態です
Our name is Potassium
私たちの名前はカリウムです
The anti-pregnancy description is probably listed here
妊娠禁止に関する説明はおそらくここに記載されています
It is also an anti-pregnancy state that can impress
それはまた、印象を与えることができる妊娠防止状態でもあります
that this generation
この世代が
Humans have a thing called fibrous meat flow
人間には繊維状の肉の流れというものがある
So-called fibromyalgia can also be seen on dogs or cats
いわゆる線維筋痛症は犬や猫にも見られます
All of you should, if you have ever had pets,
ペットを飼ったことがある方は、ぜひこうしてください。
The older your dog is, the more it will give birth
犬が高齢になればなるほど、出産の回数が多くなります
messy stuff
厄介なこと
There are a lot of fiber meat flow
繊維質の肉の流れが多い
Of course, it can be removed directly by surgery.
もちろん、手術で直接取り除くことも可能です。
This can be surgically removed
これは外科的に取り除くことができます
This can also be surgically removed
これは外科的に取り除くこともできます
But some surgical cuts can really be done with a knife
しかし、一部の外科的切除は実際にナイフで行うことができます
This incident caused many surgeons to raise a question mark
この事件は多くの外科医に疑問符を投げかけた
I give an example
例を挙げます
Some people here will get oral cancer
ここにいる人の中には口腔がんになる人もいる
Some people will swell up a big pile on this side, a big ball
こちら側に大きな山を膨らませる人もいるでしょう、大きなボール
The surgeon moved the knife when there was a big ball
大きなボールがあったとき、外科医はナイフを動かしました
it will be tim gu ass skin flesh to fill this side
こちら側を埋めるのはティム・グ・アスの皮肉だろう
But sometimes when the dirty mouth is too big
でも時々、汚い口が大きすぎるときは
It dare not move a knife
あえてナイフを動かさない
So when we first started doing anti-cancer experiments
私たちが最初に抗がん剤の実験を始めたとき
We discuss the results with the surgeon
結果について外科医と話し合います
They just want us to find a way to shrink the tumor
彼らはただ腫瘍を縮小する方法を見つけてほしいだけなのです
Then let them move the knife to do the experiment
次に、ナイフを動かして実験をさせます。
so we now
だから私たちは今
Later, we chose this anti-cancer
その後、この抗がん剤を選択しました
We make fiber meat flow HT1080 is a fiber meat flow for human beings
ファイバーミートフローを作ります HT1080は人間のためのファイバーミートフローです
Let's fight on the snail
カタツムリで戦いましょう
We can see it after playing
遊んだ後でもわかるよ
We're doing anti-facial injections
顔面への注射を行っております
injection on the tumor
腫瘍への注射
It really has something to do with the control group
それは実際にはコントロールグループと関係があります
it really has some differences
本当にいくつかの違いがあります
Difference in Tumor Size
腫瘍の大きさの違い
That's the Golden Collie
それがゴールデンコリーです
wait a minute i'll tell you
ちょっと待ってください、教えます
The golden collie later we were on the mouse and it was still the same
ゴールデンコリーはその後、私たちはマウスの上に乗っていましたが、それはまだ同じでした
we have a lot of time
私たちには時間がたくさんある
we do
私たちはそうします
It's not just experiments that want to do rats
ラットを使った実験だけが目的ではない
Experiments in my lab
私の研究室での実験
We all hope that when we're done with the fish
私たちは皆、魚を食べ終わったらこうなるだろうと願っています。
mouse that made a butterfly
蝶を作ったネズミ
and then to medium and large animals
そして中型および大型の動物へ
How about doing it on a dog or a pig
犬や豚でやったらどうだろう
In the future, if our laboratory hypocrisy fish
将来、もし私たちの研究室の偽善的な魚が
We also hope to cooperate with others
私たちも他の方と協力していきたいと思っています
Experiments that can be done on monkeys
サルでもできる実験
That's an experiment on dogs
それは犬の実験です
We can see some microsteel flow in the dog
犬の体内にマイクロスチールの流れが見られます
you can see a different dog this time
今度は違う犬を見ることができます
this is husky hal
ハスキーのハルです
Howl's dog
ハウルの犬
that's a mixed dog
それはミックス犬です
just normal
ただ普通の
Then this time, let's look at this dog
それでは今回はこの犬を見てみましょう
On the seventeenth day of the tumor on the back side of the steel gate we punched in
鉄門の裏側に腫瘍ができて17日目
A large tumor can be seen
大きな腫瘍が見られる
Then today we are Theorem Yuntian
それでは今日はテオレム・ユンティアンです
Then at the ten thousandth time
それから1万回目で
We can see that the tumor is starting to fade a bit
腫瘍が少し消え始めているのがわかります
During those nineteen days and twenty-six days
その19日間と26日間の間に
Its tumors have actually been affected by our drugs.
その腫瘍は実際に私たちの薬剤の影響を受けています。
disintegrated its tumor
腫瘍が崩壊した
On the thirty-seventh day, thirty-three day, thirty-seventh day
三十七日目、三十三日目、三十七日目
We can see that the tumor is completely gone
腫瘍が完全に消えているのがわかります
In dogs at the ninety-third day after cessation of spanking
お尻叩きをやめてから93日目の犬の場合
The dog's tumors are completely gone
犬の腫瘍は完全に消えました
The dog is alive and well and happy
犬は元気で幸せに生きています
Then we changed the PET bottle to let you tell Zhizhi
それからZhizhiを知らせるためにペットボトルを変更しました
How big is this dog
この犬はどのくらいの大きさですか
then we can know
そうすれば私たちは知ることができます
In dogs we have tumors
犬には腫瘍があります
then we have to ask another question
それなら別の質問をしなければなりません
Is it only the anti-pregnancy effect on the Bilu fish that I just ate?
たった今食べたビル魚の抗妊娠効果だけでしょうか？
So we start with what we do every day
だから私たちは毎日行うことから始めます
Real thing over the above to get another anti-pregnancy
別の妊娠防止剤を入手するための上記の本物
called TP4
TP4と呼ばれる
Then the anti-pregnancy on the turtle
カメの妊娠防止剤
it probably has...
おそらくそれはあるでしょう...
There are five types of antimicrobial cancer
抗菌薬によるがんには5つのタイプがある
But when we were doing MIC
でも、MICをやっていたときは
we can know say
私たちは言うことができます
TP4 number fourth this anti-cancer is the best
TP4 4 番目のこの抗がん剤は最高です
Its bactericidal ability is the best
最高の殺菌力を持っています
Usually it has the best bactericidal ability
通常、最高の殺菌能力を持っています
We think it's also good against cancer
ガン予防にも効果があると考えられます
so we can
だから私たちはできる
At the beginning, we chose trinity breast cancer
最初はトリニティ乳がんを選択しました
Trinity breast cancer is currently in the negative category of breast cancer
トリニティ乳がんは現在、乳がんの否定的なカテゴリーに分類されています。
The tightest in treatment
最も厳しい治療
because it is
その理由は
It has these three different
この3つの違いがあります
Variations in different genes
さまざまな遺伝子の変異
So it's troublesome on medication
だから薬のことも面倒なんだよ
Some Drugs Actually Don't Work Against Trinity Breast Cancer
一部の薬は実際にはトリニティ乳がんには効かない
In terms of treatment
治療に関しては
So we're going to fight on Lord Luo
だから私たちはルオ卿の上で戦います
Lord Luo, we can see
ルオ様、私たちには見えます
This is a general KY dye cream
こちらは一般的なKYカラークリームです
we are on the lord
私たちは主の上にいます
Added ours with KY dye cream
KY染料クリームを追加しました
Antibacterial tire of black spinach puree
黒ほうれん草ピューレの抗菌タイヤ
you can see its tumor
あなたはその腫瘍を見ることができます
start getting small
小さくなり始める
especially you can see that is to say
特に、つまり、
Only with KY dyeing cream alone
KY染付クリーム単体のみ
Now add tumor cells
次に腫瘍細胞を追加します
it's on top of whole milk
それは全乳の上にあります
it varies greatly
それは大きく異なります
but if we add we add
しかし、追加する場合は追加します
Antibacterial tires
抗菌タイヤ
Then you can see it whole
そうすれば全体が見えるよ
actually shrunk
実際に縮んだ
Including we can use some tissue immune infection
いくつかの組織免疫感染を使用することもできます
It can be seen that the IC packages in its anti-tire have been changed.
アンチタイヤのICパッケージが変更されていることがわかります。
are smaller
小さいです
There is no only KI in it.
そこには「KI」だけが存在するわけではありません。
The other parts are the so-called IC package
それ以外の部分はいわゆるICパッケージです
So we did it on the mouse
これでマウスの操作は完了です
We also use fish for verification
検証には魚も使用します
Because in Lin Hai's research, when we talk about
なぜなら、リン・ハイの研究では、私たちがそれについて話すとき、
The zebrafish is a very, very simple story
ゼブラフィッシュはとてもとても単純な物語です
very easy little technique
とても簡単なちょっとしたテクニック
So our example on the fish
魚に関する例です
The three slices of cells from which we
私たちが抽出した細胞の 3 つのスライス
Punch in from the vein of its heart
心臓の血管から突き刺す
it can be right here
ここにあるかもしれない
has a colored cell
色付きのセルがあります
Go up and type in the red IC bag
上がって赤いICバッグを入力
you can see that
それがわかります
After the chair passed
椅子過胞以後
Its IC package will grow over time
ICパッケージは時間の経過とともに成長する
to circulate throughout the body of the fish
そして魚の全身に行き渡るように
But if we add TV4 later
しかし、後で TV4 を追加すると
You'll be able to see the IC package that says it's
IC パッケージに次のように書かれているのがわかります。
actually started getting smaller
実際に小さくなり始めた
was spun off by Juju or even killed.
ジュジュによって分断されたり、殺されたりしました。
this is a short video
これは短いビデオです
This is the video we shot
これは私たちが撮影したビデオです
you can see that is to say
つまりそれはわかります
what about this fish
この魚はどうですか
when it is not treated with any medication
いかなる薬でも治療しなかった場合
This red IC is wrapped in its body
この赤いICはボディに包まれています
it grows over time
それは時間の経過とともに成長します
the fish finally exploded
ついに魚が爆発した
like just saw
ちょうど見たような
IC package if not processed
ICパッケージが加工されていない場合
then it will explode
そうしたら爆発するよ
because it's getting bigger
大きくなっているから
But what if our fish
しかし、もし私たちの魚が
We carefully put three high-roller TP4s in it
ハイローラーTP4を3台丁寧に入れました
Let's see how it turns out
どうなるか見てみましょう
What about the IC bag?
ICバッグはどうでしょうか？
it will start shrinking
縮小し始めるだろう
as time increases
時間が経つにつれて
it starts to disappear
それは消え始める
But this IC package passes through this fish
しかし、このICパッケージはこの魚を通過します
Soak in water containing anti-cigarette
抗タバコ剤を含んだ水に浸す
Its IC package was killed by our anti-yantai
そのICパッケージは我々の反ヤンタイによって破壊されました
so what do we want to do in the future
それで私たちは将来何をしたいですか
We want to talk to a doctor in the future
将来的には医師に相談したいと思っています
say these parents' breast cancer wounds
両親の乳がんの傷について言う
You can see it learns in tacit understanding
暗黙の了解で学習していることがわかります
ribs can be seen
肋骨が見える
We also hope to build a pet market
ペット市場の構築も目指します
Then let's go back to bacteria
それでは細菌の話に戻りましょう
bacteria you can see that is to say
細菌が見えるということは、
resistant bacteria
耐性菌
now we can know
今私たちは知ることができます
There are many, many, including the United States, including China, are very, very troubled by bacterial infections
米国をはじめ、中国を含む多くの国が細菌感染症に非常に悩まされています。
Especially like mainland China, I think they have recently been on the weakest magazines in recent years
特に中国本土のように、近年では最も弱い雑誌に掲載されていると思います
They talked about the emergence of drug-resistant bacteria on pigs in many areas
彼らは多くの地域で豚に薬剤耐性菌が出現していることについて話した。
so it's a headache
だから頭が痛いです
In March 2015 when Obama was President Obama
オバマ大統領だった2015年3月
he has signed a bill
彼は法案に署名しました
What is this bill for?
この法案は何のためにあるのでしょうか？
The plan of this bill is to invest a lot of money
この法案の計画は多額の資金を投資することである
Seeking scientists from all over the world to cooperate with American scientists
アメリカの科学者と協力する世界中の科学者を求めています
Conduct an antimicrobial resistant bacteria to find a new type of drug
新しいタイプの薬を見つけるために抗菌薬耐性菌を調査する
to deal with new drug-resistant bacteria
新しい薬剤耐性菌に対処するために
The bill is now signed
この法案は現在署名されています
So we're probably this is what I'm just starting out with
おそらくこれが私が始めたばかりのことです
In March 2016, a magazine told us
2016年3月に雑誌が伝えた。
A report in an editorial magazine told us that
ある編集雑誌の報道が私たちに伝えた。
Scientists in Spain find human-raised dog feces inside
スペインの科学者が屋内で人間が育てた犬の糞便を発見
A bacterium of such a family as Eubacteriaceae
真正細菌科などの細菌
So what is the existence of this bacteria?
では、この細菌の存在とは何でしょうか？
There will be a major threat to human health and benefits
人間の健康と利益に重大な脅威が生じるだろう
Everyone, don't forget what I just told you
みんな、今言ったこと忘れないでね
What happens to dog poop?
犬のうんちはどうなるのでしょうか？
Sometimes pets are in the process of excreting
ペットが排泄の途中である場合があります
we all stay at home
私たちは皆家にいます
Because I have a friend who has two small, new dogs at home
というのも、家に新しく生まれたばかりの小型犬を2匹飼っている友人がいるからです。
I see he's a dog if he poops
うんこをしたら彼は犬だとわかる
Just take the toilet paper and insert it yourself
トイレットペーパーを取り出して自分で挿入するだけです
I don't know if it was absorbed after insertion
挿入後に吸収されたかどうかはわかりません
But in the process of inserting
しかし、挿入の途中で
Think about it, if there's germs in it, it's on your hands
考えてみてください、細菌が入っているとしたら、それはあなたの手にあります
When you don't want to play when you eat
食事中遊びたくないとき
eat it in your stomach
お腹の中で食べてください
I just had a fantasy film to tell you about
ちょうどファンタジー映画について話したいことがありました
passing through the food chain or passing through excrement
食物連鎖を通過するか、排泄物を通過する
You may have these so-called drug-resistant bacteria in your body
あなたの体内にはいわゆる薬剤耐性菌が存在する可能性があります
Then the bacteria are very troublesome, that is to say
それから細菌は非常に厄介です、つまり
There are very few so-called antibiotics for muscle now to treat it
現在、筋肉を治療するいわゆる抗生物質はほとんどありません。
may be more troublesome in the future
将来的にはもっと面倒なことになるかもしれない
The other one is that you may still remember the TV of the player in the history where the player in the history had a salsa
もう一つは、歴史上の選手がサルサを披露したテレビをまだ覚えているかもしれません。
He had a cameraman shot in India before
彼は以前インドでカメラマンを撮影させたことがありました
After the shooting, when he was sent to China for treatment, he was found to have an MDM1 bacterium on his body
銃撃後、治療のために中国に送られた際、体にMDM1菌が存在していることが判明した。
MDM1 and MDM1 Bacterial Infection
MDM1 および MDM1 細菌感染症
He said that MDM1 was scared to death and now there are probably only two types of resistance that can treat him
彼は、MDM1 は死ぬほど怖がっていて、今ではおそらく 2 種類の抵抗力だけで彼を治療できるだろうと言いました。
Therefore, the current environment where humans are more enlightened is the emergence of more and more drug-resistant bacteria
したがって、人間がより啓蒙されている現在の環境では、薬剤耐性菌がますます多く出現しています。
This is our own in the laboratory, we talk to the doctors in the laboratory and colleagues in the laboratory
これは研究室にある私たち自身のものであり、私たちは研究室の医師や研究室の同僚と話しています
We ask all of us to report
全員に報告をお願いします
In the whole process of reporting to you just now, we learned from aquatic organisms
先ほどご報告させていただく過程で、私たちは水生生物から学びました。
Originally, we discovered fish disease problems from aquatic residue farming.
もともと、私たちは水生残渣養殖から魚の病気の問題を発見しました。
We want to solve the fish disease and want to replace the traditional aquatic residue farming which uses resistance data
魚の病気を解決したい、耐性データを利用した従来の水生残留物養殖を置き換えたい
Inside the traditional aquaculture
伝統的な養殖の内部
Use some chemical reagents to cure stupidity
愚かさを治すために化学試薬を使用する
Then we found out that fish is actually a very interesting thing
すると、その魚が実はとても面白いものであることが分かりました。
There is something like an antibacterial state in the fish that produces
魚には抗菌状態のようなものがあり、
Of course, there is a so-called antibacterial state in the human body
もちろん、人間の体にはいわゆる抗菌状態が存在します。
However, the experimental results we have done so far
しかし、これまでに行った実験結果では、
We discovered an antimicrobial state that we can't find in fish
魚には見られない抗菌状態を発見
Its bactericidal ability appears to be greater than some of the antibacterial states found above in humans
その殺菌能力は、人間の上記の抗菌状態のいくつかよりも優れているようです。
Also excellent, the bactericidal effect is better
殺菌効果も優れています
So we can ask for a future
だから私たちは未来を求めることができる
we already know
私たちはすでに知っています
We can probably know that in 2007
おそらく 2007 年にはそれがわかるでしょう
We found this antibacterial state
この抗菌状態を発見しました
This antimicrobial status is found on meal fish
この抗菌状態はミールフィッシュで発見されました
I just reported to you
先ほどご報告させていただきました
Sum Ya 19 years
蘇姆牙19年
We expect in 2027
2027 年に期待
We hope to push it to the clinic
クリニックに導入していきたいと考えています
But the process of these 20 years
でもこの20年の過程は
We may need to go through countless failures
私たちは数え切れないほどの失敗を経験する必要があるかもしれません
can be extended to the entire process
プロセス全体に拡張可能
Only then can we go to the clinical test in the so-called space
そうして初めて、いわゆる宇宙で臨床試験を行うことができるのです。
This is our vision for the future
これが私たちの将来のビジョンです
I also hope that all the gentlemen and ladies here today
また、今日ここにいらっしゃる紳士淑女の皆様が、
In the future, expect to be in 15 years or 20 years
将来的には15年後、20年後にはそうなるだろう
Then we can see clinically that it is such a drug
そうすれば、それがそのような薬であることが臨床的にわかります
so i just told you
だから私はあなたに言ったばかりです
There is already such a drug in 2015
2015年にはすでにそのような薬が存在しています
Emerging FDA has recognized an antibiotic that can be marketed
新興FDAが市販可能な抗生物質を認めた
A new type of antibiotic
新しいタイプの抗生物質
In the past ten or twenty years, no emerging antibiotics have emerged
過去 10 ～ 20 年間、新たな抗生物質は登場していません
But only in the last two years has this new antibiotic been produced
しかし、この新しい抗生物質が生産されたのはここ 2 年間だけです
We hope this is the Sikama company
これがシカマ社であることを願っています
We are currently selling all kinds of anti-hospital tires
現在、あらゆる種類の対病院用タイヤを販売しています
it serves as a raw material
それは原料として機能します
You can see that the Sikama company also has a number with it
Sikama 社にも番号が付いていることがわかります。
SMML0013
SMML0013
This is our anti-hospital tire
これは私たちの対病院タイヤです
It has a lot of references listed above
上記には参考文献がたくさんあります
All are the result of research and development in our laboratory
すべては当研究室での研究開発の成果です
You can go to the Sikama website if you are interested
興味があればシカマのウェブサイトにアクセスしてください
Enter the name EBCIN
EBCIN という名前を入力してください
EBIECIDIN
エビシジン
You can see that a product like ours is in the pharmaceutical factory of Sikama
当社のような製品がシカマの製薬工場にあることがわかります
There is a listing for them on sale
販売中のリストがあります
So Meng Yang hopes that this drug can become similar to this 1.4.1 in 20 years.
そこで孟洋氏は、この薬が20年後にはこの1.4.1と同様のものになることを期待している。
To help humans solve the problem of drug resistance
人間の薬剤耐性の問題解決を支援する
Of course I have to thank many students in my laboratory
もちろん、私の研究室の多くの学生に感謝しなければなりません
For example, Dr. Ding Zong, he is my doctor
たとえば、丁宗先生、彼は私の主治医です。
There is also Dr. Huang Anning, who is a business opportunity consultant.
ビジネスチャンスについて語る黄安寧博士もいる。
It seems that Dr. Ding did it.
丁博士がやったようです。
In addition, Jay Ang is an Indian student who is doing Youmenlu group induction
さらに、ジェイ・アンはYoumenluグループの誘導を行っているインド人の学生です
There is also Dr. Pan Jieyi
潘潔博士もいます
He is now at Gaohua University of Science and Technology of China
彼は現在、中国の高華科学技術大学に在籍しています。
He was experimenting with tumors in dogs
彼は犬の腫瘍の実験をしていた
And Mr. Jian Jixian also assisted us in the tumor experiment of dogs.
また、Jian Jixian 氏は犬の腫瘍実験にも協力してくれました。
There are other teachers Xu Junsheng and Li Xianping who will be in the future respectively
他に徐君生先生と李先平先生がそれぞれ将来就任予定です
Our development of anti-drugs will play a very important role
私たちの抗麻薬開発は非常に重要な役割を果たすでしょう
Of course the most important
もちろん一番大切なのは
We are currently doing experiments with pigs
現在豚を使った実験を行っています
It is all in cooperation with Mr. Wu Hongyi of Pingtung University of Science and Technology
すべて屏東科技大学の呉宏儀氏の協力によるものです。
The pig experiment depends on him
豚の実験は彼にかかっている
Because he has a beneficiary license
彼は受益者ライセンスを持っているので
Because there are many things that can help us experiment
実験に役立つものがたくさんあるので、
You just saw it
あなたはちょうどそれを見ました
In fact, at the beginning, Wu acted as an anti-court
実際、呉氏は当初、反法廷として行動した。
anti-animals
抗院態動物
The animal experiment teacher should be my junior
動物実験の先生は私の後輩のはずです
He should be younger than me by two years
彼は私より2歳若いはずです
Teacher Wu Zhangze
ウー・ジャンゼ先生
He is Mr. Wu Zhangze from the Department of Teachers, Ocean University
彼は海洋大学教師学部の呉章澤氏です。
Back when I didn't know how to do animal experiments
動物実験のやり方がわからなかった頃
I'm totally going to ask him to help me
絶対に彼に助けてもらうつもりだ
conduct similar animal experiments
同様の動物実験を行う
Including if you see burns or
火傷や
Uber Luoxuan's induction experiment
Uber Luoxuanの誘導実験
This is Huang Anning
黄安寧です
I especially want to show his photo today
今日は特に彼の写真を見せたいと思います
Because usually when we say thank you
なぜなら、私たちが「ありがとう」と言うときは、
maybe only the name
たぶん名前だけ
Everyone doesn't know what he looks like
誰もが彼の姿を知らない
you'll see he can ask him some questions
彼がいくつか質問できることがわかります
Huang Anning is excellent
黄安寧は素晴らしい
He got last year and the year before
彼は去年も一昨年も獲得した
Received the Outstanding Postdoctoral Research Award from the Ministry of Science and Technology
科学技術省優秀博士研究員賞を受賞
this is a rare award
これは珍しい賞です
He seems to be out of blue and Sheng Yilan
彼は青天の霹靂のようだ、そしてシェン・イーラン
Because I have not yet received the Outstanding Research Award from the Ministry of Science and Technology
まだ科学技術省の優秀研究賞を受賞していないため
He has already received the postdoctoral outstanding research award from the Ministry of Science and Technology
彼はすでに科学技術省から博士研究員優秀研究賞を受賞しています。
The other one is Dr. Pan Jieyi
もう一人は潘潔博士です
He's a tumor for a dog
彼は犬にとっては腫瘍だ
fat like this
こんな太った
Then our full time is the latest photoshoot
それでは、私たちのフルタイムは最新の写真撮影です
Dress a little more tiresome
もう少し面倒な服装をしてください
Then this is Dr. Ding Zhenghong, this is his wife who just got married this year
それから、こちらは丁正紅先生、今年結婚したばかりの彼の奥さんです。
Then Dr. Ding Zhenghong is doing the experiment of three-one into five cancers, and recently he is doing the experiment of lung cancer
その後、丁正紅博士は癌を 3 から 5 に分ける実験を行っており、最近では肺癌の実験を行っています。
Then we recently thought of an excellent model experiment for the treatment of lung cancer
そこで私たちは最近、肺がん治療のための優れたモデル実験を思いつきました。
I hope that in 15 or 20 years from now, it will become an emerging drug for the treatment of lung cancer.
15年後、20年後には肺がんの治療薬として発展することを期待しています。
Then I am now at 8:16, and within a minute of my post, I will tell you about my current working environment
現在、8時16分です。投稿後1分以内に、現在の作業環境についてお話します。
This is the Linhai Research Station of the Institute of Cell and Biology of the Biamine Research Institute
ここはビアミン研究所細胞生物学研究所の臨海研究ステーションです。
The Institute of Cellular and Physiological Biology has now been transformed
細胞生理生物学研究所は生まれ変わりました
It was my professor Zhihao at the beginning, today the teacher is sitting here today
最初は私のZhihao先生でしたが、今日は先生がここに座っています
At the beginning, Mr. Wu was in charge of coordinating the former head of Youxi Space County
当初、呉氏は佑西宇宙郡の前長官の調整を担当していた。
And the chairman of Jinche came to donate this land
そして金チェ会長がこの土地を寄付しに来ました
Then the reminder this time was mentioned by Dean Li Yanzhe, very beautiful Lin Hai Research Station
そして、今回のリマインダーは、非常に美しい林海研究ステーションの李延哲学部長によって言及されました。
I think it's really good to do research there, but I don't understand why many students don't come
そこで研究するのはとても良いことだと思うが、なぜ多くの学生が来ないのか理解できない
If you also ask high school students every night, we will meet with six universities, and we will come to our Linhai Research Station
高校生にも毎晩お願いしたら、6つの大学と会い、臨海研究ステーションに来ます
We are researching in Linhai, saving lives regardless of each other
私たちは臨海で研究しており、お互いに関係なく命を救っています
This seaside study is beautiful inside
この海辺の書斎は内部が美しい
At the beginning, when I went from England in 1992
初めは1992年にイギリスから来たとき
In fact, there is nothing but light here
実はここには光しかない
But now it's tree fuyin
でも今は木風音です
There's a small fountain here
ここに小さな噴水があります
this is a beautiful environment
ここは美しい環境です
This was taken when the sun was shining
これは太陽が輝いているときに撮りました
You don't see when the sun is bad and the storm is stormy
太陽が悪く、嵐が荒れているときはわかりません。
It's even scarier when it's a typhoon
台風だとさらに怖い
Because there are no tall buildings near us to go alone
近くに一人で行けるような高い建物がないので
so you can see the little gusts of those trees
木々の小さな突風が見えるように
Afraid of the sun
太陽が怖い
Then our seaside research in the whole structure
次に、全体構造の海辺の調査
You can see that there is a water and sky supply system here
ここに水と空の供給システムがあることがわかります
We are here to do experiments
私たちは実験をするためにここにいます
Then here is the dormitory with students or assistants
そしてこちらが学生やアシスタントがいる寮です
When I first went there, the students were actually quite afraid of me.
初めてそこに行ったとき、実際、生徒たちは私をとても怖がっていました。
Because I was only in my thirties at the time
当時まだ30代だったので
I am very happy to get up at 8 o'clock in the morning to do experiments
朝8時に起きて実験できるのがとてもうれしいです
Before the student came, I kicked his door
学生が来る前に、私は彼のドアを蹴りました
so i want to thank my students so much for being there with me
だから、私と一緒にいてくれた生徒たちにとても感謝したいです
Many students who do research years
研究年を重ねる学生が多い
This very good place is what idea we thought of
このとても良い場所が私たちが考えたアイデアです
Immediately, you can go in there to do experiments on aquatic life.
すぐにそこに入って、水生生物の実験をすることができます。
There are farms here, very good farms
ここには農場があります、とても良い農場です
gene transfer experiments
遺伝子導入実験
That's what the vice president just said
先ほど副社長が言っていたことです
Our laboratory has cooperated with Mr. Wu Jingqiao
当研究室は呉京橋氏と協力しました
Then carry out the research and development of the so-called fluorescent fish
いわゆる蛍光魚の研究開発を行う
Well, I didn't focus on fluorescent fish today.
さて、今日は蛍光魚に焦点を当てませんでした。
Actually, the glowfish is another question.
実は、グローフィッシュについては別の問題です。
Because I just told him that aquatic animals can get sick
なぜなら、水生動物は病気になる可能性があると彼に話したばかりだからです
So we hope that this aquatic organism has anti-smoke expression
したがって、この水生生物が煙に対する耐性を持っていることを願っています。
That's because I don't know if you've ever raised fish
それはあなたが魚を育てたことがあるかどうかわからないからです
I'm an ornamental fish. I bought ornamental fish when I was in college.
私は観賞魚です、観賞魚は学生の時に買いました。
The ornamental fish, let's say five of them, sell me 200 yuan?
観賞魚、たとえば5匹で200元売ってくれますか？
College students are poor, you should know
大学生は貧しい、知っておくべきだ
Don't snatch college students for two hundred yuan, it's easy
大学生を200元でひったくらないでください、それは簡単です
High school students are also very poor. Two hundred yuan is a lot
高校生もとても貧しい、200元は大きい
Well, I bought it and raised it for a week
はい、買って一週間育てました
If he hung up on me, I went to the boss and said
彼が電話を切ったら、私は上司のところに行って言いました。
what does he wash
彼は何を洗いますか
He said that when he cleaned his teeth, he would wash his back and his head would be thick.
歯を磨くときに背中を洗うと頭が厚くなると言っていました。
Well, then buy it, I bought it for a week and then hung it up for me
じゃあ、買ってください、一週間買って、その後放置してました
then i will go to the boss
それから私はボスのところに行きます
That boss has been bred by me in Silin one
あの上司は私がシリンワンで育てたものです
water hog jar know how to do it later
水豚の瓶は後でそれを行う方法を知っています
I'll say water pig give me some more fish
水豚、もっと魚をくれって言うよ
I was wondering why the fish died every time I bought them back for a week
1週間買い戻すたびになぜ魚が死んでしまったのか不思議に思っていた
Then I thought that after I become a teacher now
そこで考えたのは、今教師になってから
After I worked as a research scholar
研究者として働いた後
I can keep this fish alive longer
この魚をもっと長生きさせられるよ
so i just go with that
だから私はそれで行きます
At that time, we wanted to say that anti-pregnancy
当時、私たちが言いたかったのは、反妊娠です。
The transplantation is using the microscopic life-assisted mode, so that he can produce anti-pregnancy even after lifting the table
移植は微視的救命モードを使用しているため、テーブルを持ち上げた後でも抗妊娠薬を生成できます。
Then the fish will not be infected by bacteria
そうすれば魚は細菌に感染しなくなります
He can fight bacteria
彼は細菌と戦うことができる
However, this is only one of the main points
ただし、これは重要なポイントの 1 つにすぎません
Fish will not get sick as we are curators with the main purpose
私たちはキュレーターであることが主な目的であるため、魚は病気になりません
you may have forgotten
あなたは忘れているかもしれません
Because what we just talked about now is to use the synthetic ecology to do it.
なぜなら、私たちが今話したのは、それを行うために総合生態学を使用するということだからです。
Synthetic ecology has troubles and the price is high
合成エコロジーは問題があり、価格が高い
The student just told me
その学生が私に言いました
Huang Hanming told me
黄漢明は私に言いました
98% of EPI costs 780 US dollars per gram
EPI の 98% は 1 グラムあたり 780 米ドルです
So one gram is 100 people, Miliguang costs 780 US dollars
つまり、1 グラムは 100 人分であり、ミリグアンの費用は 780 ドルです
I personally feel
個人的に感じているのは
may still be a bit expensive
まだ少し高価かもしれません
So we want to use fish
そこで魚を使いたいと思います
You know that fish is warm
魚は温かいって知ってるよね
Sometimes there are hundreds of thousands of broken pieces
時には何十万もの壊れた破片があることもあります
it's scary, isn't it?
怖いですね。
soft sea tactics
ソフトシー戦術
So we want to be able to get from its
したがって、そこから取得できるようにしたいのです
its that warm
とても暖かいです
In the residual heat process
余熱工程で
In the future, these anti-halo
将来的には、これらのアンチハロー
it also extracts
それも抽出します
Because now it's easy to do protein expression
タンパク質発現が簡単にできるようになったので
Then you must be curious to ask me
それならあなたは私に尋ねたいと思っているはずです
Why don't you use a colon induction?
なぜ結腸誘導を使用しないのですか？
Because high school or college students
高校生や大学生だから
I have a speech today
今日はスピーチがあります
or friends online
またはオンラインの友達
you are on the internet
あなたはインターネット上にいます
should ask me this question
私にこの質問をすべきです
Why not use colon induction
なぜ結腸誘導を使用しないのか
or as we express the system
またはシステムを表現するとき
there are many things now
今はたくさんのことがあります
indescribable
言葉では言い表せない
we are also doing
私たちもやってます
Trying hard to do colon induction
結腸誘導を頑張っています
Anti-stunning
アンチスタン
Basically it shows
基本的にそれは表示されます
would kill yourself to behave
行儀よくするために自殺するだろう
that gut feeling
その直感
this is very troublesome
これはとても面倒です
but if fish
でも魚なら
fish it doesn't show it
魚、それは表示されません
protein
タンパク質
expressed protein
発現されたタンパク質
won't kill the fish
魚を殺しません
look how happy it is
見て、どれだけ幸せか
how fast it shines
どのくらいの速さで光るのか
so we are probably
だから私たちはおそらく
The original idea of doing anti-response posture, there are probably two kinds of ideas
反反応姿勢を行うという当初のアイデアには、おそらく 2 種類のアイデアがあります
I hope you will buy it back later
後でまた購入していただければ幸いです
call later
あとで電話します
students are poor
学生は貧しい
200 yuan is really a lot
200元って本当に高いですね
This time we have genetically transferred equipment at the Linhai Research Station is very beautiful
今回、臨海研究ステーションに遺伝子導入された設備は非常に美しいです
In the whole of Taiwan, there was no gene transfer in Qigu
台湾全土では七股には遺伝子導入はなかった
Field testing is also very missed when
フィールドテストも次の場合には非常に見逃されます。
The Linhai Research Station should cover all of Asia
林海研究基地はアジア全土にあるべきです
Or the most advanced genetically modified job in all of Taiwan or all of Asia
あるいは台湾全土あるいはアジア全土で最も進んだ遺伝子組み換えの仕事
Don't be afraid of anything running out
何もなくなることを恐れないでください
or a problem with field testing
またはフィールドテストの問題
It's still the same now we have a lot of that
それは今でも同じです、私たちはそれをたくさん持っています
the interception system or the processing system
傍受システムまたは処理システム
Then the genetic transfer at the Linhai Research Station just started
そして、臨海研究ステーションでの遺伝子導入が始まったばかりです
It's all beautiful now
今はすべてが美しいです
A very modern testing ground
非常に近代的な実験場
In the end, I still want to thank you all
最後に、やはり皆さんに感謝したいと思います
I spent so much time listening to me today
今日はとても長い時間をかけて私の話を聞いてくれました
I wish you all the best of health
皆様のご健康を心よりお祈り申し上げます
The most important thing is to welcome you all when you are free
最も重要なことは、暇なときに皆さんを歓迎することです
Come to Linhai Research Station to give us encouragement
臨海研究ステーションに来て激励してください
of course to encourage
もちろん励ますため
Someone needs to be more willing, especially a graduate student
誰か、特に大学院生にはもっと意欲が必要だ
Welcome to our inspiration research station to do research
研究を行うためのインスピレーションリサーチステーションへようこそ
Then I know that there may be some pharmaceutical companies interested in investing on the Internet
それから、インターネットへの投資に興味を持っている製薬会社もあるかもしれないと知りました。
Please come and talk to us about our accounting
会計のことならぜひご相談ください
Then how to help us develop
では、私たちの発展をどう支援するか
At least don't make me 15 or 20 years, just make me dead for 15 years
少なくとも私を15年や20年にしないで、15年死なせてください
Then help everyone to be more promising on some antibacterial effects
そうすれば、誰もが抗菌効果の面でさらに期待できるようになります。
Thanks
ありがとう
Thank you, thank you very much Dr. Chen for a very wonderful presentation
チェン博士、とても素晴らしいプレゼンテーションをありがとうございました
Then I wonder if you have anything to ask Dr. Chen about?
それでは、チェン博士に何か聞きたいことはありますか?
later
後で
The anti-Qing platform is the one that is moving overnight
反清のプラットフォームは一夜にして動いているものである
Just to avoid that leftover field
残ったフィールドを避けるためだけに
Does that mean
それは〜を意味しますか
A chair that lives where the night is cloudy
曇りの夜に生きる椅子
It may find that the more powerful the viewing platform
視聴プラットフォームが強力であればあるほど、
like a mud mound or something
泥塚か何かのように
Would it be better than being in a stone pound chair
ストーンパウンドチェアに座るよりは良いでしょうか？
this theory is good
この理論は良いです
but i don't know
でも分からない
Because I only feel that the whole fish
魚全体だとしか感じないので
This should be in terms of evolution
進化論的にはこうなるはずだ
Because the whole fish evolution process
なぜなら、魚の進化のプロセス全体が
i can't tell you
言えません
Do you live in the dirty water at night?
夜は汚れた水の中で暮らしていますか？
Although I just said
今言ったばかりなのに
But that's universal
でもそれは普遍的なものだよ
if it is like this
このような場合
I think the fish in our Sifenxi should be more resistant
うちの四分渓の魚はもっと抵抗力があるべきだと思う
There should be many
たくさんあるはずです
Everyone seems to see a sign
誰もが兆しを見ているようだ
No arrest, right?
逮捕は無いですよね？
At present, it is just looking for ecology from Mimisheng
現在は耳生の生態を調べているところです。
Or other animals have early
あるいは他の動物も早くから
that's the first question
それが最初の質問です
The second question is to say
2番目の質問はこう言うことです
Ecology Can Kill Morbidity
エコロジーは病気をなくすことができる
Will it affect normal cells?
正常な細胞にも影響を与えるのでしょうか？
The third one seems to me that I heard you said that in that
3番目は、あなたがその中でそう言ったのを聞いたような気がします
So far, it has not been formally used in humans
これまでのところ、人間では正式に使用されていません。
like this
このような
But I seem to have heard on the Internet that there are direct sellers selling this product
しかし、インターネットでこの商品を販売している直販業者があると聞いたような気がします。
don't know you know what this is all about
分からない、これが一体何なのか知っているのか
do you have a problem
なにかもんだいがありますか
Anti-morbid at certain concentrations
特定の濃度で抗病的作用がある
above a certain concentration
一定以上の濃度
It will be normal cells will be destroyed according to the disaster
災害に応じて正常な細胞も破壊される
kill normal cells
正常な細胞を殺す
so we usually
だから私たちは普段
I'm giving a popular science speech today
今日はポピュラーサイエンスの講演をします
So I didn't spend a lot of time fixing it here
したがって、ここでの修正にはあまり時間をかけませんでした
we have a few in the lab
研究室にいくつかあります
So if students or researchers in our lab
したがって、私たちの研究室の学生や研究者が
We will first test for cytotoxicity
まずは細胞毒性を検査します
this is the first step
これが最初のステップです
The second step is when it comes time to develop the drug
第 2 ステップは、薬を開発するときです。
to test some of its body
体の一部をテストする
Like GOTGPT or those things, see what dosage is best
GOTGPT などのように、最適な投与量を確認してください
This answers your first question, his political cells are toxic, there is nothing wrong
これがあなたの最初の質問の答えです、彼の政治細胞は有毒です、何も問題ありません
But Dependent still depends on different anti-pathological conditions, I have read some reports
しかし、依存症は依然としてさまざまな抗病理学的条件に依存している、私はいくつかのレポートを読んだ
Some antipathogens are non-cytotoxic
一部の抗病原体は細胞毒性を持たない
But he has the function of so-called cellular immune regulation
しかし、彼はいわゆる細胞性免疫調節の機能を持っています
Its bactericidal effect is not that strong
殺菌効果はそれほど強くありません
Usually less toxic means that its ability to kill bacteria is not so strong
通常、毒性が低いということは、細菌を殺す能力がそれほど強くないことを意味します
So we have to adjust a very good dosage, just like you take Kangshengsu
したがって、あなたが康生水を服用するのと同じように、非常に適切な投与量を調整する必要があります。
You also have to find a good dose
適切な用量も見つける必要があります
Excessive health vitamins can also cause
健康ビタミンの過剰摂取も原因となる可能性があります
bad situation happens
悪い状況が起こる
right
右
The second problem is that I forgot
2番目の問題は忘れてしまったことです
do you mind talking to me again
もう一度話してくれませんか
It seems that the Internet is selling that thing in the market
インターネットであのものが市販されているようです
I don't know how to answer this question
この質問にどう答えればいいのかわかりません
because i told you
私が言ったから
In fact, you can see that Sikamai is also sold in the market
実はシカマイも市場で売られているのがわかります
You can buy our anti-momentum
私たちの反勢いを買うことができます
Yes, it is for sale
はい、販売中です
But let me say one more thing
でも、もう一つ言わせてください
In fact, ten years ago, when I was in the anti-mobility posture,
実際、10年前、私が反流動性の姿勢にあったとき、
At that time, there were not many people in the world doing anti-movement
当時、世界中で反対運動をする人はそれほど多くありませんでした。
not not many people
多くの人ではありません
It is in Japan, mainland China, Taiwan, Southeast Asian countries
日本、中国本土、台湾、東南アジア諸国にあります
These Asian countries do not have a lot of manpower to go
これらのアジア諸国には行くべき人員があまりありません
Mainland China's anti-transportation attitude is really poisonous
中国本土の運輸反対の姿勢は本当に有害だ
I heard they have become a special zone to do anti-movement
反対運動をするための特区になったそうです
So they called an anti-motion state Sikobon
そこで彼らは反運動国家をシコボンと呼んだ
It is the anti-motion state obtained on the forehead
額に得られるアンチモーション状態です
Has been sold to the so-called Tianjian toilet
いわゆる天津トイレに販売されています
Tian Jian went down
ティエン・ジャンは倒れた
can be bought
買える
yes , so i am a little worried too
はい、だから私も少し心配です
Will there be waist resistance in the future?
今後は腰抵抗もあるでしょうか？
yes it is available for purchase
はい、購入可能です
but that's not
しかし、そうではありません
no
いいえ
Not American DA or Taiwan
アメリカの検事局でも台湾でもない
Taiwan's Drug Inspection Bureau has licensed it to be sold in the form of drugs
台湾の麻薬監督局は麻薬の形で販売することを許可した
Like we went to buy from Sikama
シカマに買いに行ったみたいに
It's just a substance sold to you
それはあなたに売られた単なる物質です
No one can control how you use it
誰もあなたの使い方をコントロールすることはできません
Ask for advice
アドバイスを求める
just saw that on video
それをビデオで見たばかりです
Fish with cancer in antibacterial water
抗菌水でがんを患った魚
That cancerous tumor can disappear
その癌性腫瘍は消える可能性があります
This means that the antibacterial state can cure cancer
これは、抗菌状態が癌を治療できることを意味します
so should we eat more fish
じゃあもっと魚を食べるべきか
But the fish is different from the fish you just had
でもその魚はさっき食べた魚とは違う
Do other fish also have antibacterial properties?
他の魚にも抗菌作用があるのでしょうか？
Thanks
ありがとう
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
Antibacterial water is also present in your body
抗菌水は体内にも存在します
but we don't eat people
でも私たちは人を食べません
We eat fish for
私たちが魚を食べるのは、
It is hoped that in the future through the process of aquaculture
将来的には養殖のプロセスを通じて、
I have another interesting story for you
もう一つ興味深い話があります
Some people are collecting what I just said
私が今言ったことを集めている人もいます
Isn't everyone immune to fishing?
みんな釣りに無縁じゃないの？
Some people are collecting fish immunity
魚の免疫を集めている人もいます
Then he took it as a sort of antibacterial substance
それから彼はそれを一種の抗菌物質として捉えました
down to do business
ビジネスをするために
then all fish will have an antibacterial status
そうすればすべての魚が抗菌状態になるでしょう
As far as I can tell since you're not eating fish
私が知る限りでは、あなたは魚を食べていないので、
is aquatic organisms
水生生物です
So that oyster will also have an antibacterial status
牡蠣も抗菌状態になるように
But among all the fish species
しかし、すべての魚種の中で
Why do I especially choose grouper and silky fish
私が特にハタ類と烏骨魚を選ぶ理由
Because grouper and blackbone are very important aquaculture industries in Taiwan
ハタと黒骨は台湾の非常に重要な水産養殖産業であるため
I hope that the process of giving a speech today is not just about
今日のスピーチのプロセスが、ただのことではないことを願っています。
We use the antibacterial state to do it in medical medicine
抗菌状態を医療に利用します
I also want to let everyone know
私も皆さんにお知らせしたいです
Aquaculture is actually Taiwan's inherent aquaculture such as grouper and black bone fish
養殖は実はハタや黒骨魚などの台湾固有の養殖です
A breed that has been in Taiwan for so long
台湾に古くから存在する犬種
The industry also hopes to attract everyone's attention
業界もみんなの注目を集めたいと考えています
Later you go out on the street
その後、通りに出ます
Please choose more of these kinds of juban fish and five countries fish to eat
十番魚と五国の魚をもっと選んで食べてください
The multi-selected juban fish and five countries fish to eat
厳選十番魚と五国の魚を食べる
It can also promote the vigorous development of our flood farming industry
また、洪水農業産業の活発な発展を促進することもできます。
They all eat the fish bred by this Shuizi sheep
彼らは皆、この水子羊が育てた魚を食べます。
Are you eating too much healthy food?
健康的な食べ物を食べすぎていませんか？
fish in water
水の中の魚
In fact, the government now does so-called barcode tracking
実際、政府は現在、いわゆるバーコード追跡を行っています。
I don't know that you actually learned from the process of the ten-fish industry
実際に十魚産業のプロセスから学んだのかは知りません
As long as you are in Taipei Agricultural Products
台北にいる限り農産物
It has a similar
同様のものがあります
Similar to that black Q barcode
あの黒いQバーコードに似てる
According to the future it will have a production history
将来に応じて生産履歴が残ります
Tell you which factory this fish came from
この魚がどこの工場から来たのか教えてください
Then it seems that it will also test whether the fish has health vitamins
その後、魚に健康ビタミンが含まれているかどうかもテストするそうです
The government is actually doing a good job of checking the gates now.
実際、政府は現在、ゲートのチェックをきちんと行っています。
That's just something I remember happening before some decamp farms
それは、いくつかのキャンプ農場の前で起こったことを覚えているだけです
It seems that there is no way through this system
このシステムを通過する方法はないようです
However, it was found to contain
ただし、含まれていることが判明しました。
Many chemicals or antibiotics
多くの化学物質や抗生物質
So I still encourage everyone to eat more fish
だから私は今でも皆さんにもっと魚を食べることを勧めています
Please trust Taiwanese aquaculture farmers
台湾の養殖業者を信頼してください
Let's see if Yuntai cooks it
ユンタイが料理してくれるか見てみましょう
It's also an interesting question
それも興味深い質問ですね
recently
最近
The deputy dean asked an interesting question
副学部長は興味深い質問をしました
Do you all want to eat fish after fighting the Taizhu?
皆さんは太竹と戦った後は魚を食べたくなりますか？
I also encourage everyone to eat more fish today
今日は皆さんにももっと魚を食べることをお勧めします
Will there be no small children in the future after resisting the Taizhu?
太祖に抵抗した後、将来小さな子供は残らないのでしょうか？
Just cook at 100 degrees C
100℃で焼くだけ
Only recently did this result
この結果が出たのはつい最近のこと
And published on PoS1
そしてPoS1で公開されました
After cooking at 100 degrees C, when you did not cook
100℃調理後、調理をしなかった場合
About double the MIC will kill bacteria
MICの約2倍で細菌を死滅させることができる
After cooking, it still has the effect of killing bacteria
調理後も殺菌効果が持続
We have an anti-response too
アンチ反応もあるよ
very interesting
とても興味深い
so we just saw that
それで私たちはそれを見ました
That TP4 that can heal the beautiful feeling
美しい気持ちを癒してくれるあのTP4
you know the acid in the stomach is sour
胃酸が酸っぱいのは知っていますね
PH4 or something
PH4とか
But it still has bactericidal ability in acidic environment
しかし、酸性環境下でも殺菌力を発揮します。
10 minutes to 60 minutes
10分～60分
It still has a bactericidal effect
殺菌効果もまだあります
We put it in the Vickers tube, put it in the water and boil it for a hundred degrees, instead of closing the whole water
水を全部閉めるのではなく、ビッカース管に入れて水の中に入れて100度で沸騰させます。
Just put it in two Vickers tubes and let him cook like this
2本のビッカースチューブに入れて、このように調理してもらうだけです
Turns out he's still active, which I find interesting
彼はまだ活動していることがわかり、興味深いと思います
So we want to know that under normal conditions, Teacher Xu Junzhen is actually a teacher from National Taiwan University
したがって、通常の状況では、Xu Junzhen先生は実際には国立台湾大学の教師であることを知りたいのです
He was before, before he had the whole structure of doing anti-motion
彼は以前、アンチモーションを行うための全体的な構造を備える前にいた。
He has made the structure under long-term temperature, but I have not told him what kind of changes will happen to the structure after being cooked for a hundred times.
長期の温度下で構造を作っているが、100回加熱すると構造にどのような変化が起こるかはまだ教えていない。
Why does it still have the ability to sterilize bacteria, listen up
なぜ細菌を殺菌する能力があるのですか、聞いてください
Hello, that is, I have seen one before, which is vitamin D, which can improve the body's anti-mobility effect
こんにちは。以前見たことがありますが、それはビタミン D で、体の運動抑制作用を改善することができます。
Is this true?
これは本当ですか？
why? thanks
感謝なんて、どうして
Vincent book D?
ヴィンセント本D?
Yes, Vincent Shu D
はい、ヴィンセント・シューD
Then Pei Baowang published it in the series with the prefix N?
その後、ペイ・バオワンは接頭辞「N」を付けてシリーズとして出版しました。
I have seen a similar article, but I did not read carefully
同様の記事を見たことがありますが、よく読んでいませんでした
this question...
この質問...
I don't know either
私も知りません
you ask me like this
あなたは私にこのように尋ねます
Teacher Bao Wang D can help me add
Bao Wang D 先生が追加を手伝ってくれます
I can guess, because general antibiotics...
一般的な抗生物質なので推測できますが...
Which paragraph does this follow?
これはどの段落に続きますか?
right
右
General antibiotics its structure
一般的な抗生物質の構造
just... sorry
ただ…ごめんなさい
This antibiotic has no specific structure for its structure
この抗生物質にはその構造に特定の構造はありません
But when it encounters the state of Zilong sex
しかし、それがZilongセックスの状態に遭遇すると、
It will be easier to appear as it just said
先ほども言ったように出やすくなります
Two sides... that is, one side is Zilong sex
両面…つまり片面は子龍セックスです
One side is the structure on the front
片側が前面の構造です
Also in the time of pure water dragon sex
純水ドラゴンセックスの時も
It is not this structure
この構造ではありません
Then encounter...Wen Shengshu D's purple dragon...
そして遭遇…ウェンシェンシュウD、紫龍…
Or the environment of Zilong sex
またはZilongセックスの環境
It is easy to show that the effective structure
効果的な構造を示すのは簡単です
So relatively its bactericidal ability will be better
そのため比較的殺菌力が高くなります
Go ahead... also for us...
どうぞ…私たちのためにも…
Our understanding of antibacterial ecology is like this
抗菌生態に対する私たちの理解は次のとおりです
Just mentioned the heating issue
先ほど暖房の問題について触れました
In fact, this protein is a structure of more than 20 amino acids
実はこのタンパク質は20個以上のアミノ酸が結合した構造になっています。
Assuming that because its structure is originally no structure
元々構造が無いのでそう仮定すると
Only when encountering this environment will the structure
この環境に出会って初めて構造が変化します。
So after you group it, its structure is messed up
グループ化すると構造がめちゃくちゃになる
But when it encounters a child-like environment
しかし、子供のような環境に遭遇すると、
it structure comes back
構造が戻ってくる
So maybe this can be explained by
おそらくこれは次のように説明できるでしょう
Why is it still active after grouping
グループ化した後もアクティブであるのはなぜですか
that just mentioned
それは今言った
if you eat this
これを食べたら
May be hydrolyzed by my stomach acid
胃酸で加水分解されるかも
Of course it won't help
もちろん役に立ちません
But stomach acid is what I just
しかし、胃酸は私がただのものです
that I guessed next is
次に私が推測したのは
We just made that time mention
そのときのことについて言及したばかりです
It is in the sour environment that it has
それは劣悪な環境にある
In the process of the protein not working
プロテインが機能しなくなる過程で
It still retains the activity of its MIC
現在もMIC活動を維持している
So now we are surprised
それで今私たちは驚いています
why does it have that activity
なぜそのような活動があるのですか
after the group
グループの後
Either in an acid environment or a subtractive environment
酸性環境または減法性環境のいずれか
We have done B 2 to 14
B 2 ～ 14 を完了しました
24,6,80,12,14
２４、６、８０、１２、１４
We found between 4 and 12
4から12の間で見つかりました
it still holds
それはまだ残っています
After being released in a private yard for a period of time
一定期間私家の庭に放した後
He still picks it up to make MIC, he still has the energy to sterilize
彼は今でもMICを作るためにそれを拾い、殺菌するエネルギーをまだ持っています。
we have done recently
私たちは最近やりました
very interesting
とても興味深い
I do not know why either
理由は私にも分かりません
Maybe it's really similar to what Mr. Liao Wenwei said
おそらくリャオ・ウェンウェイ氏の言っていることと非常に似ていると思います。
Hello, teacher
こんにちは先生
I want to ask you a question
質問があります
i saw the dog test
犬の検査を見ました
After he beat him in with that MAS
彼がMASで彼を打ち負かした後
We saw that the teacher still has
先生がまだ持っているのを見ました
Do the treatment in Bless Cancer
Bless Cancer で治療を行う
Does he have the same plan like this
彼もこのような同じ計画を持っていますか
Let women's Bless Cancer
女性にがんを祝福させましょう
He was hired by MVT
彼はMVTに雇われました
Does he have the same effect
彼にも同じ効果がありますか
If this treatment
この治療なら
he is a little scary
彼は少し怖いです
Is there such a plan
そんな計画はありますか
What kind of treatment is his treatment
彼の治療はどのようなものですか
that kind of dog
そういう犬
he's actually quite funny
彼は実際とても面白いです
because we are experimenting with rats
ネズミを使った実験をしているからです
we're on cell experiments
私たちは細胞実験中です
we actually feel
私たちは実際に感じています
The antibacterial tires you just saw
さっき見た抗菌タイヤ
it is the way to go the cell statue
それが細胞像への道です
but you see in animals
でも動物には見られるよ
In fact, there is data similar to cell necrosis
実際、細胞壊死と同様のデータがあります。
so we
だから私たちは
At that time, I didn't go down to ask
その時は聞きに行かなかった
exist...
存在...
Because it is very troublesome in Taiwan
台湾ではとても面倒なので
It's a dog experiment
犬の実験です
Our dog is not
私たちの犬はそうではありません
Everyone imagines it made with beagle
誰もがビーグルで作ったと想像します
Because when we made this plan
なぜなら、この計画を立てたとき、
COA said that if we use beagle to make
COAは、ビーグル犬を使って作れば、と言いました。
It absolutely swallowed up our plan.
それは私たちの計画を完全に飲み込んでしまいました。
I think...
私が思うに...
So because there are...
だから、そこには...
We are doing a project in that agricultural bio-type fruitamine therapy plan
農業型バイオ型フルアミン療法計画でプロジェクトを行っています
So but one thing it allows us to do is
しかし、それによって私たちにできることが 1 つあります。
This dog is a stray dog
この犬は野良犬です
Or a dog brought by the master
または主人が連れてきた犬
Those four groups can let us do this experiment with their consent
これら 4 つのグループは、同意を得てこの実験を行うことができます
But when it came, some tumors were very large.
しかし、実際に発症すると、一部の腫瘍は非常に大きくなっていました。
when we call in
私たちが電話するとき
After a while that Petite
しばらくすると、そのプチちゃんは
Because of the volume we play sometimes
時々再生する音量のせいで
To be honest, it doesn't have a lot of dogs
正直に言うと、犬の数はあまり多くありません
So sometimes that air
だから時々その空気は
I think it might look a bit
少し見えるかもしれないと思います
just overdose
ただ過剰摂取するだけ
so overdose
とても過剰摂取です
Its anti-morbidity is actually inside the cells
その抗罹患性は実際には細胞内にあります
I think there is really something
本当に何かあると思う
As the gentleman just said, it has cytotoxic effect
先ほど紳士が言ったように、細胞毒性がある
So after he killed the cells
それで彼が細胞を殺した後
A condition that becomes necrotic
壊死状態になる状態
That's on Lu Lai
それはルーライにあります
Because our family has not yet
私たち家族はまだそうではないので、
We can only be Lulai on the ancestors
私たちは祖先のルーライにしかなれません
Lu Lai, we haven't done animal experiments yet
ルー・ライ、私たちはまだ動物実験を行っていません
because we also want to find
私たちも見つけたいから
There are dogs that specialize in Lulai
ルーライ専門の犬がいる
or someone willing to take it to an animal hospital
または動物病院に連れて行きたい人
and then treated by a physician
その後医師の治療を受ける
His dog is Lu Lai
彼の犬はルー・ライです
so-called trinity breast cancer
いわゆるトリニティ乳がん
we have to wait again for this
これをまた待たなければなりません
So in the whole animal experiments
つまり、動物実験全体において
We currently have no more detailed information to tell you
現時点ではこれ以上お伝えできる詳細な情報はありません
But just that picture
でもその写真だけ
The one with breast cancer and the one with breast cancer
乳がんになった人と乳がんになった人
In fact, the picture of the breast cancer is on the Internet
実際、乳がんの写真がインターネット上にあります
We may all see
私たち全員が見るかもしれません
girl getting breast cancer
乳がんになる女の子
If you accidentally get triple breast cancer
誤ってトリプル乳がんになってしまったら
And then at the end not very early on
そして最後に、それほど早い段階ではありませんでした
In the end, her wound will fester
結局、彼女の傷は化膿するだろう
you can see the bones
骨が見えます
In principle, we just hope
基本的にはただ願うだけです
hope to develop some kind of
何らかの開発を期待しています
You can see that we have information about Shao Shangchang
シャオ・シャンチャンに関する情報があることがわかります。
We want to develop some kind of paint
ある種の塗料を開発したい
because it can be applied to her wounds
彼女の傷にも塗れるから
It can also close the wound and kill cancer cells
傷をふさぎ、がん細胞を殺すこともできます
Now we just want to do experiments like this in the future
今後はこのような実験をしていきたいと思っています
But the trouble with this experiment is that you have to
しかし、この実験の問題点は、次のことを行う必要があることです。
I just reported to you
先ほどご報告させていただきました
Just to find the crooked dog
曲がった犬を見つけるためだけに
Then there's Trinity Breast Cancer again
そしてまたトリニティ乳がんが発生する
Then you can't use rice to cut milk
そうなると、牛乳を切るために米を使うことはできません
so this will cost
したがって、これには費用がかかります
So Su Wu shepherds for 18 years
ソー・スーウーは18年間羊飼いをしている
I may have to pasture for 20 years
20年間放牧しなければならないかもしれない
that's the factor
それが要因です
To wait for
を待つ
Some of our experiments
私たちの実験の一部
You may have seen me talking here for less than an hour
私がここで 1 時間未満話しているのを見たことがあるかもしれません
more than an hour
1時間以上
People say that one minute on stage and one minute off stage
ステージ上で 1 分、ステージから降りると 1 分と言われます
We've probably been doing it for ten years
たぶん10年くらいやってる
right
右
So please forgive our speed
だから私たちのスピードを許してください
why so slow
なぜそんなに遅いのか
I also wish it could be faster
私ももっと早くできればいいのですが
Thanks
ありがとう
i want to ask
聞きたいです
May I ask how much EP1 a fish will have
魚のEP1はどのくらいになるのか聞いてもいいですか？
It is anti bacteria peptide
抗菌ペプチドです
a fish
一隻魚
finish your question
質問を終えてください
I have no idea
何も思いつきません
that or
それか
If you want to get imminigrant
移民を取得したい場合
How many fish do you need to extract to get
入手するには何匹の魚を抽出する必要がありますか
good question again
また良い質問です
We don't extract from fish
魚からは抽出していません
We use the model of synthetic cards to
合成カードのモデルを使用して、
use ecology
用生態
Ecos can now be crafted with Ecosynthesis
エコ合成でエコを作成できるようになりました
It is a machine that can synthesize
合成できる機械です
No need to kill a chicken and take its soft
鶏を殺して柔らかいものを取る必要はありません
We can use machines to synthesize ecology
私たちは機械を使って生態系を合成できる
Excuse me
すみません
If you eat fish
魚を食べるなら
Which part do you want us to eat to be more rewarding?
どの部位を食べたらより食べ応えがありますか？
Is it fish skin?
魚の皮でしょうか？
or what to eat
または何を食べるか
good question
良い質問
I don't know how to answer
どう答えてよいかわかりません
When I first started thinking about this topic
初めてこのテーマについて考え始めたとき
I hope everyone can eat more fish in the future
将来的にはみんながもっと魚を食べられるようになりますように
Then promote the development of our residual farming industry
そして、私たちの残存農業産業の発展を促進します
that kidney
その腎臓
Attracted by this topic
この話題に惹かれて
Know the residual farming industry
残された農業産業を知る
It's an interesting creature in language
言語的には面白い生き物だ
sorry i have one last question
申し訳ありませんが、最後に質問があります
Excuse me
すみません
If we only treat this
これだけ扱うと
Antibacterial peptide to bacteria
Antibacterial peptide給細菌
and in a test tube
そして試験管の中
Then eventually, do you think it will still have a Resistant in the end?
では、最終的には耐性が残ると思いますか?
Yes, this is something I havent dared to talk about just now, and I havent talked about it yet
そう、これは今あえて言えなかったし、まだ話したこともなかったのですが、
Now based on the current literature report, it is reported that there is no antibacterial bacteria produced in nature
現在の文献報告に基づくと、自然界には抗菌性細菌は存在しないと報告されています。
But we are in the laboratory, and some literatures have reported
しかし、私たちは研究室におり、いくつかの文献が報告しています
Antimicrobial bacteria can be produced in the artificial mode in the laboratory
抗菌細菌は実験室で人工的に生成可能
I just had a picture to tell you
ちょうどお伝えしたい写真がありました
In the antibacterial state, it will actually enter the bacteria, from DNA to RNA, to the process of protein
抗菌状態では、DNAからRNA、タンパク質のプロセスに至るまで、実際に細菌に入ります。
that also produces what's called an antimicrobial state of bacteria
それは細菌のいわゆる抗菌状態も生み出します
But in our lab I once had a research creature that was also interesting
しかし、私たちの研究室では、かつて、これも興味深い研究生物を飼っていました。
I asked him to help me deal with the bacteria with EPI
私は彼にEPIで細菌に対処するのを手伝ってくれるように頼んだ
At the beginning, did we pull the MIC from 1/10 or 1/4?
最初はMICを1/10から引いたのか、1/4から引いたのか。
Keep dealing with us until the end seems to be able to reach 10 times the MIC
MICの10倍に達しそうなまで最後まで付き合ってください
But bacteria can still freeze eggs
しかし、細菌は依然として卵を凍結させることができます
But I didn't continue to do the experiment later, because originally this experiment should be doing the so-called molecular biology tool called Potonomic,
しかし、私はその後実験を続けませんでした。本来この実験はポトノミックと呼ばれるいわゆる分子生物学のツールを行うべきだったからです。
It is to let the so-called two-dimensional capacitance sudden change interview to see what protein has changed,
いわゆる二次元静電容量急変インタビューをさせて、どのタンパク質が変化したかを見るというものですが、
But because of the relationship between ability and financial resources at that time, we did not continue to do it.
しかし、当時の能力と資金の関係で、それを続けることはできませんでした。
Lets still quote what I just said at the beginning, we want to be like Switzerland, our laboratory is orderly like Switzerland,
私が冒頭で言ったことをまだ引用しましょう、私たちはスイスのようになりたい、私たちの研究室はスイスと同じように秩序立っています、
We want to be small and beautiful, so I focus on doing other things and keep asking,
小さくて美しくなりたいから、他のことに集中して、求め続けます。
Should it still be the skin, that is, the skin or the intestinal tract is the main source?
やはり皮膚、つまり皮膚が主な発生源であるべきでしょうか、それとも腸管が主な発生源なのでしょうか？
No, the anti-smoke carbon actually comes from other sources. For example, there is an anti-smoke carbon called Hip-Cidine.
いいえ、防煙炭は実際には他の供給源から来ており、たとえば、Hip-Cidine と呼ばれる防煙炭があります。
H-E-P-C-I-D-I-N, which is produced by the liver,
肝臓によって生成されるH-E-P-C-I-D-I-N、
It just came out of human urine when it was discovered
発見されたときは人間の尿から出てきたばかりだ
Payback here is posted on JB7
ここでのペイバックはJB7に掲載されています
It is from human urine to perform the so-called HPLC
いわゆるHPLCを行うのは人間の尿からです
Then found a Farcman inside
すると中にファルクマンがいた
It found that there is a so-called antibacterial effect
いわゆる抗菌効果があることが分かりました
So it still thinks to go back and trace this gene
したがって、この遺伝子を遡って追跡することをまだ考えています
Where does its product come from?
その製品はどこから来たのでしょうか?
Our more interesting question is to say
私たちのもっと興味深い質問はこう言うことです
all the fish in every organ
すべての魚がすべての臓器に
In fact, we do RNA analysis
実際にRNA解析も行っています
We can know that there will be so-called EPI in almost every place
ほぼすべての場所でいわゆるEPIが存在することがわかります。
But on the epidermis, it produces more RNA
しかし、表皮ではより多くのRNAが生成されます。
right
右
professor again
また教授
The professor advocated to eat more of this oxygen fish
教授はこの酸素を含んだ魚をもっと食べるよう主張した
Because it contains antibacterial properties, right?
抗菌作用が含まれているからですよね？
In this way, if we often eat this oxygen fish contains antibacterial
このように、私たちがよく食べると、この酸素を含んだ魚には抗菌作用が含まれています。
Does that reduce our overall inflammation?
それは私たちの全体的な炎症を軽減しますか？
Eating more fish will make the body less prone to inflammation
魚をもっと食べると体が炎症を起こしにくくなる
Is it this way
こうですか
Thanks
ありがとう
I dare not talk about this issue again
この問題については二度と話すつもりはありません
But I think eating more fish is good
でももっと魚を食べるのは良いことだと思う
Because there are DH and NTM on the fish
魚にはDHとNTMがあるので
Then it seems that the fish is also better than the four-horned animal. Will I be killed?
そうすると、魚も四角獣より優れているようですが、殺されてしまうのでしょうか？
Fish is also a better source of meat than four-horned animals.
魚は四角動物よりも優れた肉源でもあります。
It's also better quality
品質も良くなりました
I think it should be like this
こうあるべきだと思う
Eating more fish, I think, should have some effect on immune inflammation
もっと魚を食べると、免疫炎症に何らかの効果があるはずだと思います
Because we usually eat cod liver oil?
普段肝油を食べているからでしょうか？
Cod liver oil has been verified to have some DHEPA
タラ肝油にはある程度の DHEPA が含まれていることが確認されています
Our laboratory has conducted experiments on EPA and DHEPA in inhibiting immune inflammation
私たちの研究室では、免疫炎症を抑制するEPAとDHEPAの実験を行ってきました。
Well, we have recently verified that it really suppresses immune inflammation.
さて、私たちは最近、それが本当に免疫炎症を抑制することを検証しました。
ok four people please
はい、4人お願いします
Hello, teacher
こんにちは先生
What I want to ask is the ecological center
私が聞きたいのはエコロジーセンターです
Have you thought about modifying several amino acid regions to change its function like this?
このようにいくつかのアミノ酸領域を改変してその機能を変えることを考えたことはありますか?
Recently, edited by Paver in the so-called Science Report
最近、いわゆるサイエンスレポートでペイバーによって編集されました
On a magazine called Scientist Report
サイエンティスト・レポートという雑誌に掲載されました
Someone used two Modify and two amino acids
誰かが 2 つの Modify と 2 つのアミノ酸を使用しました
It can be successfully expressed in the protein expression system
タンパク質発現系で正常に発現可能
we are doing this too
私たちもこれをやっています
But for now, I still want to go back to what you said just now that we want to do
でも今はまだ、あなたが今言ったことに戻りたい、私たちはやりたいと思っています
But we're still waiting for the mayor's financial and human input.
しかし、私たちは依然として市長の財政的および人的投入を待っています。
Let me add so as not to mislead everyone that you can be sterilized just to eat fish
皆さんに誤解を与えないように付け加えさせていただきますが、魚を食べるためだけでも不妊手術は可能です。
When you have liver disease, it's not just eating fish that can cure liver disease
肝臓病の場合、肝臓病を治すには魚を食べるだけではありません
Then the food goes down and is digested by the food
その後、食べ物は下に行き、食べ物によって消化されます
Basically this has been broken down
基本的にこれは分解されています
The case of becoming a single low and single short paragraph counts
単一の低い段落数と単一の短い段落数になる場合
He may no longer have the ability to fight bacteria
彼はもう細菌と戦う能力を持っていない可能性があります
Please don't mislead everyone
皆さん誤解させないでください
just mentioned
先ほど述べた
Some antimicrobial products are commercially available
いくつかの抗菌製品は市販されています
That thing depends on how you use it
それは使い方次第です
if you just eat it
ただ食べるだけなら
I believe it's probably 99.99% broken down
おそらく99.99%壊れていると思います
probably useless
おそらく役に立たない
So don't take it easy on the Internet
だからインターネットで気を緩めないでください
Which antibacterial product to buy can treat what
どの抗菌製品を買えば何が治療できるのか
And you eat and fight
そして、あなたは食べて、戦います
completely different from a certain effect
ある効果とは全く違う
And the bacteria it kills may be completely different infections
そして、それが殺す細菌はまったく異なる感染症である可能性があります
So don't buy it for yourself
だから自分で買わないでね
right
右
Recently, there seems to be a so-called marine ecology on the Internet
最近、インターネット上にいわゆる海洋生態学があるようです
A lot of people
多くの人々
I saw on the Internet that there is a so-called marine ecology for sale
いわゆるマリンエコロジーが販売されているのをインターネットで見ました
eat and fight
食べて戦う
Actually it's a different story
実はそれは別の話です
What I said today is that I hope everyone eats fish
今日私が言ったのは、みんなに魚を食べてほしいということです
Eating fish and killing bacteria like you are two different things
あなたのように魚を食べることと細菌を殺すことは別のことです
Yes, Mr. Liao thinks
はい、リャオ氏はこう思います。
But I encourage everyone to eat fish because I hope to be able to
しかし、私は皆さんに魚を食べることをお勧めします。
Everyone attaches great importance to the industry of water beach farming
誰もが水辺養殖産業を非常に重視しています
I hope everyone eats more fish
みんながもっと魚を食べるといいですね
So I add carbon dioxide to beef
そこで牛肉に二酸化炭素を加えます
So eating more fish won't cause this kind of problem
したがって、魚をもっと食べてもこのような問題は起こらないでしょう
My purpose is to hope that everyone can eat more fish
私の目的は、みんながもっと魚を食べられるようになることです
Pay more attention to the aquaculture industry
水産養殖産業にもっと注目してください
Best Seas
最高の海
please teach me
教えて下さい
Chen Jiaojiao
チェン・ジャオジャオ
Do you think the three are easier to obtain
この３つは入手しやすいと思いますか？
Or is it better to say that these three effects are better?
それともこの３つの効果が優れていると言ったほうがいいでしょうか？
good question
良い質問
In fact, because when I went to Linhai Research Station,
実際、臨海研究ステーションに行ったとき、
I still have to tell my history
まだ自分の歴史を語らなければなりません
When going to Linhai Research Station
臨海研究ステーションに行く場合
At first we just hoped
最初はただ願っていた
Make a little contribution to Taiwan's aquaculture industry
台湾の水産養殖産業に少しでも貢献してみませんか
The aquaculture industry was
水産養殖業は、
On the turtle fish is the albino coccus infection
カメの魚にはアルビノ球菌感染症があります
The grouper is infected with viruses and bacteria
ハタはウイルスや細菌に感染している
So I started with these two types of fish as animals for my experiments
そこで、実験用の動物としてこれら 2 種類の魚から始めます。
Do you know what I mean
分かりますか
right
右
Do you have any other questions
他にご質問はありますか
Since grouper
ハタ以来
These fish have their own antimicrobial ecology
これらの魚は独自の抗菌生態を持っています
But these bacteria can still infect these animals
しかし、これらの細菌は依然としてこれらの動物に感染する可能性があります
So it must be said that only ecologists kill a certain bacterium
したがって、特定の細菌を殺すのは生態学者だけであると言わざるを得ません。
But other bacteria still won't kill
しかし、他の細菌はまだ死滅しません
So this fish can also be infected by bacteria
つまり、この魚も細菌に感染する可能性があります
right
右
Teacher Liao asked a question
リャオ先生が質問しました
It is similar to antibiotics that have the so-called broad-spectrum effect and load-carrying effect
いわゆる広域作用と負荷作用を持つ抗生物質に似ています。
The antibacterial ecology is the same, there is a so-called broad-spectrum antibacterial ecology
抗菌生態は同じであり、いわゆる広域抗菌生態が存在します。
Antibacterial Ecology with Loading Effect
ローディング効果による抗菌エコロジー
I just gave that example
私はちょうどその例を挙げました
That is to say, a HIP-STIDM was found on humans
つまり、HIP-STIDMがヒトで発見されたということです。
HEP-CIDM
HEP-CIDM
We also found this antibacterial ecology on turtle fish
この抗菌生態はカメウオでも発見されました
It is the so-called load-carrying antimicrobial ecology
いわゆる負荷を伴う抗菌エコロジーです。
For example, it may only kill certain types of bacteria
たとえば、特定の種類の細菌のみを殺す可能性があります。
API can actually kill many, many bacteria
API は実際に非常に多くの細菌を殺すことができます
it's like in our movie
まるで私たちの映画のようです
It is a broad-spectrum bacterium
広域スペクトルの細菌です
Broad-spectrum antimicrobial ecology
広範囲の抗菌生態学
Not for this fish will it be
この魚には当てはまらないでしょう
It may take further research to find out.
それを知るにはさらなる研究が必要になるかもしれません。
May I ask that Kang Juntai how to lock the pathogen
カン・ジュンタイに病原体をロックする方法を聞いてもいいですか
what he wants
彼が望むもの
Just said a certain concentration
一定の集中力を言ったばかりです
In fact, Shanghai will destroy normal cells
実際、上海は正常な細胞を破壊します
at lower concentrations
より低い濃度では
Just like normal cells and pathogenic cells
正常な細胞と病原性細胞と同じように
How does Kang Juntai lock the cells of pathogens?
カン・ジュンタイはどのようにして病原体の細胞をロックするのでしょうか？
then go from his pattern
それから彼のパターンから離れてください
you asked another very interesting question
あなたはまた非常に興味深い質問をしました
This is what we have said
これが私たちが言ったことです
Because hand in hand to many molecular mechanisms
多くの分子機構と密接に関係しているため、
simply means to say
単に言うことを意味します
Kang Juntai has the so-called water-clearing and water-carrying properties
カン・ジュンタイは、いわゆる水を浄化し、水を運ぶ性質を持っています
On normal cells and on bacteria
正常細胞と細菌について
The composition of his cell membrane or cell arm is the same as that of normal cells
彼の細胞膜または細胞腕の構成は正常な細胞の構成と同じです
normal cells are different
正常な細胞は違う
So Kangkang will suffer from this
だからカンカンはこれで苦しむことになる
This leading force to
この導く力は、
so-called bacterial
所謂的細菌的
It's the reason why the positive and negative are finer
ポジティブもネガティブも細かい理由です
he will be drawn to it
彼はそれに惹かれるだろう
will not be compared with normal cells at low concentrations
低濃度では正常細胞と比較されません
done at very low concentrations
非常に低い濃度で行われる
interaction like this
このようなやりとり
right
右
what's the problem
どうしたの
students high school students have
高校生が持っている生徒
Yes or no
はい、もしくは、いいえ
Excuse me
すみません
can i ask the professor a question
教授に質問してもいいですか
That's Kang Juntae
カン・ジュンテさんです
mainly in the cell volume
主に細胞体積で
still in cell pool
まだセルプール内にあります
that's what i saw
それが私が見たものです
Someone on the internet wrote that
ネット上の誰かがこう書いていました
He is the cell
彼は細胞だ
After bacteria eat
細菌が食べた後
Then use the container to enter the food bubble
次に、容器を使用して食べ物の泡に入ります
break down the bacteria
細菌を分解する
You said that Kang Juntai eats bacteria
カン・ジュンタイは細菌を食べると言いましたね
no is
いいえ、です
that's the time
それがその時です
Test cells
テストセル
dead cells
死んだ細胞
after eating the bacteria
細菌を食べた後
it forms a food bubble
それは食品バブルを形成します
Then dissolve and go in
それから溶けて入ります
Is the antibacterial Taiwan really in the solution?
台湾の抗菌剤は本当に解決策になるのでしょうか？
no antibacterial Taiwan in solution
溶液中に抗菌台湾は含まれていません
I am in antibacterial Taiwan it will not go to dissolve
私は抗菌台湾にいます、それは溶けません
Because there are too many enzymes in the solution
溶液中に酵素が多すぎるため
it will take it away
それはそれを奪ってしまうだろう
will break it down
それを打ち破るだろう
So why did we just talk about antibacterial tables
では、なぜ今抗菌テーブルについて話したのでしょうか。
Will you be afraid of the role of eggs from plums?
梅の卵の役割を恐れますか？
because you have a good idea
あなたには良いアイデアがあるから
I
私
you ask him this question
あなたは彼にこの質問をします
I ask to do
するようお願いします
I have another question for you
もう一つ質問があります
In the process of cancer drug development
抗がん剤開発の過程で
do you know
あなたは知っていますか
There will be liposomes
リポソームもあるだろう
buy so-called chemically synthesized drugs
いわゆる化学合成薬を買う
like cranberries
クランベリーのような
Then the cranberries are brought into the cells
次に、クランベリーが細胞内に持ち込まれます
When cancer cells go inside
がん細胞が内部に入ると
It marks the time when the drug is brought into the cancer cell
薬剤ががん細胞に取り込まれる時間を示します
Why is this chemically synthesized drug
なぜこれが化学合成薬なのか
it can kill that cancer cell
それはその癌細胞を殺すことができます
because it is in the so-called Libosome
いわゆるリボソーム内にあるため
That's when liposomes are brought in
そこでリポソームの出番です
Usually go to the Lysofone you just mentioned
通常は、先ほど述べた Lysofone に行きます。
close up
閉じる
In the agricultural media, it is a chemically synthesized drug, so it will not be hydrolyzed by these
農業用培地では化学合成薬剤であるため、これらによって加水分解されることはありません。
At the beginning, our laboratory also wanted to wrap it in the liposome, hold it in the hand, and send it to the cell.
私たちの研究室も当初はリポソームに包んで手に持って細胞に届けたいと考えていました。
Then through the same picture is to kill the cells, but it is so dead, this experiment has not been done
次に、同じ写真を通して細胞を殺すことですが、細胞は死んでいるので、この実験は行われていません
After discussing with the teachers of the Chemistry Institute, it was just when Mr. Li Xianqiong was discussing
化学研究所の先生たちと話し合った後、ちょうど李先瓊先生が話し合っているときでした。
He told me that this will definitely be borrowed by the agricultural media and agricultural disintegration, so this way is not feasible
これは間違いなく農業メディアに借りられて農業が崩壊するので、この方法は無理だと彼は言いました。
Exactly like this, so we didn't do cell experiments
まさにこれと同じなので細胞実験はしませんでした
I speculate that the anti-disease is secreted outside the so-called cells, and kills the bacteria first
私は、抗疾患物質がいわゆる細胞の外に分泌され、最初に細菌を殺すのではないかと考えています。
Then some giant cells will gobble it up, like this
そして、いくつかの巨大な細胞がそれを飲み込みます、このように
It should not be in the agricultural media
農業メディアに載せるべきではない
Excuse me, professor, I would like to ask a question
すみません、教授、質問したいのですが
It was the time when the Anti-Tai Army committed suicide and killed the Aijin continuation package
反台軍が自殺して愛人継続パッケージを殺害した時だった
He does not need to adjust a specific concentration to produce a specific cell
特定の細胞を生成するために特定の濃度を調整する必要はありません
just be able to kill him
ただ彼を殺すことができる
So the question I want to ask is
それで私が聞きたい質問は
Can he kill this?
彼はこれを殺すことができるでしょうか？
Will he be able to hit the ground running or will he stay there
彼は本格的にスタートできるだろうか、それともそこに留まるだろうか
Other Aijin Sequel Packs
その他の藍人続編パック
Then consider the study of love stem cells
次に、愛の幹細胞の研究を考えてみましょう
Is it very likely that he will relapse
彼が再発する可能性は非常に高いですか
You asked a good question too
良い質問もしましたね
Now that you are admitted to the graduate school, can you come to my laboratory?
大学院に入学したので、私の研究室に来てくれませんか？
do an experiment
実験をする
Pull the graduate first
先拉一下研究生一下
really good question for you
あなたにとって本当に良い質問です
meeting
ミーティング
He can't kill all the love cells
彼はすべての愛細胞を殺すことはできません
so we just saw
それで私たちはちょうど見たところです
This is what I told my lab colleagues
これは私が研究室の同僚に言ったことです
This is what our first generation thought
これが私たちの初代が考えたことです
In fact, the first generation of this process
実際、このプロセスの第一世代は、
everyone is very
みんなとても
Everyone can general laboratory
誰でもできる一般実験室
We now have ideas for second-generation drug development
第二世代の医薬品開発のアイデアが得られました
However, since it has not been made
ただし、作っていないので、
So it's not convenient for me to talk to you here
だからここであなたと話すのは都合が悪い
You can wait a minute and I will tell you later
ちょっと待ってください、後で教えます
Because many people will know
知ってる人も多いだろうから
then we are a small laboratory
それなら私たちは小さな実験室です
you just saw there were only a few cats
猫が数匹しかいなかったことがわかりましたね
my thoughts i think there are a lot of fresh ideas
私の考え 新鮮なアイデアがたくさんあると思います
It's not really suitable for you to listen to it under the hall broadcast
実は、ロビー放送の下で聴くのには適していません。
except i made it
私が作った以外は
I'll tell you when I succeed
成功したら教えます
We want to develop second generation drugs
第二世代の医薬品を開発したい
It can be similar to the current targeted drug
現在の標的治療薬と類似している可能性がある
it only targets cancer cells
がん細胞だけをターゲットにする
to the cancer cell
がん細胞に
Antibacterial tires will kill that special cancer cell
抗菌タイヤはその特別ながん細胞を殺します
including cancer cells as well as bacteria
細菌だけでなくがん細胞も含まれます
That is to say, from the broad-spectrum antibacterial
つまり、広範囲に作用する抗菌タイヤから
Make it antibacterial only against certain bacteria
特定の菌に対してのみ抗菌する
Antibacterial tires against certain bacteria
抗菌タイヤ
Biotechnology should be able to do it now
バイオテクノロジーなら今でもできるはずだ
but we're going to try
でも試してみましょう
None of us should have done this
私たちの誰もこんなことをすべきではなかった
we have seen cooperation
私たちは協力を見てきました
wait we have that idea
待ってください、私たちにはその考えがあります
So when I'm done
それで終わったら
if successful
成功した場合
I will listen
私は聞くつもりです
I'll wait and hear what we think
待って、私たちの意見を聞きます
but you don't
でもあなたはそうしません
He'll be like an antibody, a mutation that's never passed on
彼は抗体のようなもの、決して受け継がれない突然変異になるだろう
mutation mutation
突然変異 突然変異
disease resistance
耐病性
he will
彼は
he will be like
彼はこうなるだろう
Won't
しません
He's basically an elite constant
彼は基本的にエリートの常連だ
he won't mutate
彼は変異しないだろう
you say something like
あなたは次のようなことを言います
similar bacterial mutation
同様の細菌の突然変異
right
右
He doesn't look like a bacterial mutation
彼は細菌の突然変異のようには見えません
The question is like an antibody
質問は抗体のようなもの
Is it an antibody
抗体ですか
Object antibody
対象抗体
Antibody V region
抗体 V 領域
V region
V領域
Does the row produce antibodies?
行けば抗体が生成されますか?
no
いいえ
Will there be a change
変化はありますか
But
しかし
The anti-disease he does not use antibodies
彼が抗体を使用しなかった抗疾患
idea to sterilize
殺菌するというアイデア
He went directly to sterilize by himself
彼は自分で直接消毒しに行きました
He said it will keep changing
彼はそれは変わり続けるだろうと言いました
Won't
しません
Antibodies won't
抗体はそうではありません
Because he's an ATGOTTG he's a certain gene product
彼は ATGOTTG なので、特定の遺伝子産物です
Do bacteria have a gene?
細菌には遺伝子があるのでしょうか？
bacteria
細菌
Bacteria will target this type of antibacterial state to
細菌は、このタイプの抗菌状態をターゲットにして、
Yes, so this time I just repeated the report to you
はい、今回は改めてご報告させていただきました
Now in the state of artificial synthetic mode in the laboratory
現在実験室で人工合成モードの状態
We are bacteria that can find antimicrobial states
私たちは抗菌状態を見つけることができる細菌です
However, there has not been any report in the natural environment
ただし自然環境では報告がない
tell us that there are bacteria that are resistant to certain antibacterial states
特定の抗菌状態に耐性のある細菌が存在することを教えてください
I just think it's in the process of evolution
まさに進化の途中だと思う
Maybe there is a change in the antibacterial status
もしかしたら抗菌状態が変化しているのかもしれません
isn't it? in the process of evolution
そうですよね、進化の過程で
Yes, you want to talk about how the antibacterial state evolves
はい、抗菌状態がどのように進化するかについて話したいのですね
To the question of the evolution of the antimicrobial state
抗菌状態の進化の問題に対して
I can't answer you
答えられません
Although I have always wanted to find us Lin Yaying
私はいつも私たちを見つけたいと思っていましたが、リン・ヤイン
Just when another teacher called Mr. Taitian
ちょうど別の先生がタイティアン先生に電話したとき
He seems to be doing evolution
進化してるらしい
Then I want to ask him how to evolve to do experiments
それから私は彼に実験を行うためにどのように進化するかを聞きたいです
But I still have to go back
でもまだ戻らなきゃいけないんだよ
Because every day in the laboratory we are still a small satellite TV small scale
なぜなら、毎日研究室にいる私たちはまだ小さな衛星テレビだからです。
We can only do research on certain research topics
特定の研究テーマについてのみ研究を行うことができます
yes too many questions
はい、質問が多すぎます
What everyone was concerned about just now is that
今みんなが気になっていたのは、
Will this antibacterial tire be treated for a long time?
この抗菌タイヤは長期間にわたって処理されますか?
Those pathogenic bacteria were originally effective
それらの病原菌はもともと効果があった
Being resistant to drugs is like resisting a dead pig
薬物に抵抗するのは死んだ豚に抵抗するようなものだ
I personally think this means
個人的にはこういう意味だと思う
The main antibacterial tires have a large drug resistance
主な抗菌タイヤは耐薬品性が高い
It has a stop model and a copped model
ストップモデルとコッピングモデルがあります
That is, it will impress the membrane
つまり、膜に影響を与えます
This is mainly if the drug resistance does not
これは主に耐性が発達していない場合に発生します
But antibacterial tires are still consistent
しかし、抗菌タイヤは依然として一貫しています
DNA replication or RNA routing
DNA複製またはRNAルーティング
or as a transfer of blank paper
または白紙の転送として
This is very similar to the mechanism of action of most current antibiotics.
これは、現在のほとんどの抗生物質の作用機序と非常に似ています。
If its mechanism of action is mainly limited to that part
作用機序が主にその部分に限定されている場合
Antimicrobial resistance may develop
抗菌剤耐性が発現する可能性がある
So it's two big
だからそれは2つ大きいです
Most of them are to destroy the membrane, in simple terms, to impress
それらのほとんどは、簡単に言えば、印象を与えるために膜を破壊することです。
So cell disease bacteria, the cells inside the cells will be lost
それで細胞病菌、細胞内の細胞が失われます
So the bacteria will be the first to meet, they won't be able to survive
したがって、細菌は最初は生き残れません
Second, the membrane is moved too much, it robsick
第二に、膜が動きすぎるとロブシックになります。
So in EM, you can see that many cells have been ground by cells and are not brittle
EM では、多くの細胞が細胞によって粉砕されており、脆くないことがわかります。
The cell chips come out, so these are two types
セルチップが出てくるのでこの2種類
It all depends on you, Kang Xintai, which one is the main mechanism of action?
すべてはあなた次第です、カン・シンタイ、主な作用機序はどれですか？
mostly impressed
ほとんど感動した
so this answers your question
これであなたの質問に答えます
Well, the two times are about the same
まあ、その2つの時間はほぼ同じです
So now before it's over I'll announce that it's the next time
だから終わる前に、次回があることを発表します
grateful
感謝
Director of Guoxing Lin Zuoyuan
國興林祚原間所長
The award is the memory of Japan in Taiwanese folk beliefs
この賞は台湾の民間信仰における日本の記憶である
I hope everyone will join in the night
夜はみんなも参加してくれると嬉しいです
sure there will be more than enough in this dinner
きっとこのディナーでは十分すぎるほどあるだろう
then we introduce again
それではまたご紹介します
Thank you again Dr. Chen for your wonderful association
チェン先生、素晴らしいご縁に改めて感謝申し上げます。